[music]
Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
Heat.
Heat. Heat. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. [music]
[music]
Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Heat. Heat.
Heat
[music]
Heat. Heat.
Heat
[music]
up here.
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat. [music]
Heat.
[music] Heat.
[music]
Heat.
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
Heat. [music]
[music]
Heat.
Heat. [music]
[music]
Heat.
Heat. [music]
[music]
Heat.
>> [music]
>> Heat. [music]
Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Is it time?
It is time for us to do what we have
been doing and that time is every day.
>> We'll see what happens. We'll know in a
very short period of time. But it looks
like it could be something that will be
uh not good. [music] Believe me, not
good.
>> I am a dissident.
[music]
Don't move.
I'm saying no here. Palunteer.
Palunteer. Paler.
[music]
>> Seriously, we need to release the FC
list.
>> I am not a church boy.
[music]
>> They are full on vampires.
>> They hate [music] our beef. They hate
our beef.
They hate our beef because our beef is
beautiful and theirs is weak. [music]
Not good. Believe me, not good.
[music]
>> Hello dissident. Welcome one and all to
a Sunday evening edition of the do
dissident podcast. My name is Katon
Weiss. Thanks everybody for being here
tonight. Great crowd to start things
off. Look at that. We got a thousand
strong filing in on YouTube already. 358
over on Rumble. Please smash that like
button for us. Let's get an even bigger
crowd in here. Of course, Russell is
overseas. You all know where Russell is
right now. Oh, he is on his group tour
of China with an American group tour
doing red-blooded American things over
there in China. Uh but uh I have uh a
terrific guest uh joining me uh for the
program this evening. We've been seeing
a lot of his work lately on X. We've
been featuring a lot of his banger
tweets. He's a political commentator. He
is the host of Liberty Lockdown on
YouTube, Rumble, as well as your
favorite podcast platform. Pleasure to
welcome to the program for the first
time, Clint Russell. Clint, great to
meet you.
>> Russell's not out of the country. He's
still here. I got you, guys.
>> Okay. Yeah, there you go. Yeah. Well,
it's nice to meet you, man. I love your
backdrop. I thought that was San Diego
because you got the Padres's hat on all
the time, but uh you are a refugee from
California. Is that correct?
>> Yep. Yep. That's what radicalized me. I
am a lockdown refugee.
>> A lockdown refugee. That's right. So,
you know, I think many of our audience
are familiar with you and your work, but
some may not be since we sli swim in
slightly different circles. We're more
in the lefty lane and you're more in the
libertarian lane, but we're both against
child sex trafficking in World War II.
So, hey, uh that's something, right? Uh
so, could you just tell us a bit about
your show and and how you got into this
space? just want to flesh out a few more
of those uh details about how you got in
this uh crazy independent media game.
>> Sure. Uh I mean very very uh shorthand
version of it. I my I'm a second
generation libertarian. My dad was a
libertarian. Uh taught me about you know
Mises Rothbard when I was growing up in
the '90s. And so when Ron Paul came
around I was obviously thrilled to see
someone who was popularizing my ideas.
Uh he was then you know blacklisted and
abused by the media and the political
apparatics. and I immediately was
radicalized further against the duopoly
and then the lockdowns happened. Uh I
was running a mortgage company at the
time was very successful retired because
I could no longer you know project
economically forward and then I started
the podcast as just a mechanism to
venting and it's become what it is. So
it's weird weird arc but that's what
happened.
>> Yeah. Well I mean it it took off uh
fairly quickly I guess. I mean you made
a big name for yourself big enough to
appear at the libertarian convention in
2024. This was a big moment. Uh you were
on stage here with Dave Smith and Vive
Rama Swami. There was of course uh you
know a big pitch that Trump made to the
libertarian party for their endorsement
and so there was a big debate at the
time whether libertarians uh should
support Donald Trump or not. So here you
were at the time
>> we should we should not have [laughter]
Okay,
>> keep going. [gasps]
>> Hindsight's 2020 for all of us, man. Uh
but uh here at the time you were
expressing your reservations about that
and uh this went over really well in the
room. So here's you on stage with V Rama
Swami
too a few things that drew some booze.
What do you think, Clint, is like the
biggest obstacle for most of these
people in the room, if you could speak
on their behalf or for yourself that is
what you just can't get over the hump to
say, okay, I I can swallow this pill
that we may agree on some issues with
Donald Trump. Certainly, all the right
people hate him, but I can't pulling the
lever for him.
>> Yeah. Um, it's actually it's interesting
because I was thinking about that right
before we came out here and it was
actually a t a tagline in your speech
about turning words into action. The
issue has been that the GOP throughout
my entire life has not turned words into
action. They haven't. [cheering]
[applause]
>> They [cheering]
They've pro They've promised to defend
They've promised to defend the
Constitution when
I'm going to die before they do it. I
mean, this is this is my deep-seated
concern. They They also talk about
limited government. They talk about
ending the wars. They talk about
bringing our troops home. When when it's
not happening. So, the reason the
Libertarian Party is as viable as it is,
the reason that Donald Trump and
yourself and even RFK are here this
weekend is because the the election
margins are so thin that you guys need
us. And I appreciate that you're willing
to come and talk to us because there's
not real animist particularly between
you and I. I have a tremendous amount of
respect for you. But there is a
tremendous amount of animosity between
myself and the GOP who has ran around
talking as if they're Ron Paul and then
governing as if they're John McCain.
[cheering]
That's that's a first. Thank [cheering]
you.
[applause]
>> So that really brought the house down.
So tell us what happened after that. Did
you eventually support Trump? And can
you kind of lay out um whether you did
or didn't? Um the timeline of the sort
of Trump libertarian love story, how it
started through how it ended, assuming
it's pretty much over at this point. I
mean, I don't really see any
libertarians, even like, you know, Angel
McCart. I don't see anybody really
pumping him at this point.
>> No. Um Yeah. I mean, I don't know if
there was ever a full-on love story, but
I I basically caved like one week before
the election. and I just said, "Look, I
think that the proxy war in Ukraine is
so dangerous that we've got to we've got
to punish the Democrats. Like, we've got
to they have to lose." Um, so that was
really what made me conclude it. It
wasn't that I was buying into the hype
as to Trump being some, you know, cost
cutting small government maven or
anything like that. Um, but I did
appreciate that he hadn't started any
major wars in his presidency. And I
thought that there was a chance that he
was actually interested in negotiating
peace with Putin. Um I hoped even though
I said in the episode where I announced
that I was going to vote for him, I I
hoped that he was not as much in the
employee of Israel as I thought he might
be. Um and I said I think I said in that
episode that like worst case scenario
with Donald Trump is war with Iran.
[laughter]
Um
[snorts] and uh and we got it. We got
it. So,
>> you're a prophet there. Wow. So, yeah. I
mean, it's funny because in the runup to
the 2024 election. Um, you know, I I
voted for Jill Stein for similar
reasons, like to punish the Democrats
because of the genocide in Gaza. There
was a group of Palestinian activists in
in Michigan whose express intent was to
get enough votes for Jill Stein in
Michigan to deny Kla Harris the state
and the race. like we were very explicit
in our intent that uh you know the
Democrats need to pay a price for the
genocide in Gaza, but also just the
whole four years in general. I mean the
war in Ukraine obviously horrible and um
you know the the Biden administration
was an administration really defined by
uh censorship, suppression and war. And
so um it made everybody desperate to
vote for something else. turned out they
voted for censorship suppression and
war.
>> Yeah, I guess the only uh difference is
that there's less nuclear weapons
involved potentially. Um but yeah, and I
the reason I didn't mention Gaza is
because I just didn't see Trump as being
much better on that than Biden.
Obviously, I wanted that to end, too.
I'm very
>> very seriously anti-war. Um, but yeah, I
mean the Democrats are a train wreck and
I thought that Trump had a chance of
being at least 20% better and I think
he's maybe
even now. So, I'm I'm very disappointed.
I forgot to open up our conversation
with uh alahu Akbar and happy Easter
because that's that's what we that's
what we do in America now. Uh,
>> exactly.
>> I mean, exactly.
>> What a what an utterly bizarre thing to
post on Easter morning. I I saw a tweet
uh today. Could you imagine if Barack
Obama had said praise be to Allah on
Easter Sunday? Could you imagine the
reaction to that?
>> It would have been less surprising.
>> Unbelievable. Just unbelievable. But we
we will get into that. We will get into
that uh in in due time. But what do you
think was the tipping point for a lot of
libertarians with Trump? Was it
>> the uh one big moment like the first war
with Iran, the 12- day war? I know
that's when that's when Dave Smith
publicly came out and said he should be
impeached and removed. Was it the
Epstein memo in July? Was it just over
time realizing how subservient he was to
the Israel the Israelis? Was it
anti-free speech actions like detaining
the student protesters for their
anti-Israel opinions? Cuz all of these
seem like grave offenses against
libertarianism. When did the damn break
in your estimation?
>> Yeah, for me the dam broke when he said,
"Wait, wait, wait. We're still talking
about Epstein." Yeah, that was it.
>> He said, "Go ahead and answer the
question if you want, but I just think
that we're really wasting our time
talking about FC. I was radicalized like
like a light switch when that happened."
I was like, "Oh, this guy is fully
compromised." So, for me, it was that
and the 12-day war. I mean, that was so
egregious. Um, and honestly, the Charlie
Kirk assassination, his behavior after
that, and then the full-blown Iran war
was just like I don't know any
libertarian that's still playing footsie
with this guy at this point. So, it's
>> it's interesting. Sorry to cut you off.
Go ahead.
>> Oh, no. I I don't even know where I was
going. Go.
>> No, it's okay. No, it's interesting that
you mentioned Charlie Kirk. Can you Can
you elaborate that on that a bit more?
Was it just his his demeanor in terms
of, hey, look at my ballroom is almost
done. Yeah, Charlie Kirk is a great guy.
Or was it uh you know uh because I
personally don't know what happened. I
don't think any of us can know what
happened, but I think there's a lot more
to that
>> than they told us. So yeah, when you say
the Charlie Kirk assassination, what
specifically about that?
>> Well, it's both. I mean, it's the
callousness with which he talks about
him uh or really the lack of talking
about him. He doesn't seem to have any
concern with him at all. It actually
reminds me a lot of Butler,
Pennsylvania. you know, these are these
are like things you would expect Trump
to harp on a lot.
>> He doesn't talk about them at all.
>> And I think that tells you a lot. You
know, it's not you can't trust what
Trump has to say, but you can you can
read by what he won't discuss. And to
me, that's like a really telling sign as
to the the true nature behind Charlie
Kirk's assassination. Like you said
though, I I don't have a firm answer to
it. Uh but then it's also just like the
obvious betrayal of Charlie's legacy.
The fact that he was such an ardent u
opponent to the war in Iran that he
spent two full days during the 12-day
war or right before the 12-day war
trying to stop it and then the entire
TPUSA kind of zio that happened
afterwards along with Donald Trump, his
entire cabinet and the broader GOP
influencer class. They're all just such
traders.
>> Yeah. You know, it's it's really
interesting that you mentioned the lack
of time devoted to talking about Charlie
Kirk. You see that in the Butler thing
as well. Like, yeah, it it it is very
telling what they don't want you to
focus on. Like, if you remember his
State of the Union, he starts the thing
off by going on for like six or seven
minutes about the hockey team because
they won their hockey game. Sentence
after paragraph after paragraph, ovation
after ovation about the hockey team.
Then he mentions Charlie Kirk. He goes
to Erica Kirk for like 45 seconds. And
that's it. He moves off of it. You know,
7 minutes for the hockey team, one
minute for the guy who got killed, one
of your most ardent supporters, one of
your most effective organizers. I mean,
whatever anybody thinks of Charlie Kirk,
there's no denying he was one of the
MVPs of that campaign. It's hard to
imagine Trump winning the kind of
margins he won with young people,
especially young men, without Charlie
Kirk. And yeah, hardly a word. Hardly a
word about it. It was bizarre.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And I I would imagine that
Charlie had a lot to do behind the
scenes with booking all of those
independent podcast uh you know spots
for Trump just cuz he had all those
contacts. So
>> yeah, I mean it's just to me it's just
egregious. You know, the way that they
kind of used and discarded Charlie um
really radicalized me. And then the what
I think is happening is a cover up. So
that's radicalizing me further. Um and
but like I said, I still don't know who
did it actually. It could have been our
government, could have been foreign
intelligence. I'm really not sure. Uh,
and it's and it could have been um,
sorry, I wanted to say Krooks. What's
his name? I'm blanking on it.
>> Oh, well, Krooks was the Butler guy and
then Tyler Robinson is the Charlie.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, Robinson certainly could
have been involved and I think that
there's a good chance that he was, but I
just find it very hard to believe that
that's all there is to that story. I
mean, there's so there's so much
weirdness to it. Um, I don't know if you
want to get into that. It's very deep.
So we can we can keep moving. But I just
overall
>> and for the record I I disagree with
Charlie Kirk on a lot of things. I was
not like some obviously
>> Charlie Kirk's supporter by any stretch.
But the one thing that really brought
him and the libertarians together is
that he seemed to have really learned
the lesson of the war on terror.
>> Not to the point that libertarians have
where they're going to actually go
against Trump and burn bridges to try
and prevent another disaster because
Charlie did not do that after the 12-day
war. But privately he did do that and I
think that that speaks highly to his his
courage and his character. Something
that everybody else in his organization
unfortunately including his wife has not
demonstrated to carry that torch forward
on. Like there's just no one doing it.
>> Yeah, for sure. That and uh freedom of
speech too. I mean when uh the the
congressman Mike Lawler, he introduced
that anti-boycott bill making it
essentially a criminal act to join
international boycots against Israel. uh
Charlie Kirk and Marjorie Taylor Green
and Thomas Massie who we're going to
talk about in just a minute. Uh they
they were the three biggest voices
leading the charge against that and the
bill got scrapped. The bill was not
brought to the House floor. Um you know
now there's no big I mean there there's
no there's no big star within the MAGA
movement who is speaking out against
this war and you have to imagine he
would have. I mean, he and certainly
TPUSA is not at this point. And I think
that is uh shameful. Uh regardless of
their culpability, and I'm not saying
they're culpable. I'm saying even best
case scenario,
they're certainly dishonoring Charlie
Kirk's legacy by not speaking out
against this war, which we know for a
near fact he would have.
>> Yep. Exactly. Uh, I do want to correct
one thing because I still I still view
Tucker Carlson as being MAGA and he's
been about as outspoken as anybody and
as successful as anybody in the
right-wing commentariat when it comes
to, you know, opposing this war and and
really criticizing Trump in a very
effective manner. So, but yes, uh, which
is also why I pray for Tucker Carlson
daily and I'm very fearful that they're
going to take him out, too.
>> That is true. Like it's hard to
determine now who's MAG or who not. Like
when CNN came out with that poll, 100%
of MAGA Republicans support Trump. Well,
I guess if you still call yourself MAGA,
maybe that means you support Trump. Like
Candace Owens was MAGA at some point.
She just tweeted out before we went on
air, this is a satanic administration.
6:24 p.m. She just fired around.
>> So I love it. I mean, and for the
record, I don't agree with uh a lot of
the things that Candace has done in
terms of this investigation. Um even
though I think that it's been very
valuable, some of the things she's
highlighted, but I love her courage. I
mean, I love how much of a fire, you
know, just a blowtorrch she really can
be. Um, and I'm the same with Tucker
Carlson. I disagree with him
particularly on economics a lot and but
I just love the fact that he's like he
seems to be seriously committed to this
path in a way that I did not expect at
all. Um, and maybe I'm biased because
he's, you know, he's scare quotes
platformed my good friends Dave Smith
and Scott Horton. Um, and that's
convinced me that he's the real deal and
not a CIA plan or something like that.
uh you know, they're convinced, so I'm
convinced for now.
>> Well, uh if the CIA is writing that uh
referral against him, we'll see if that
comes comes down the pike. That'll be a
a big tell. Uh one guy who has shown a
lot of courage is Thomas Massie. You
have been a vocal supporter of his,
especially now since Trump is coming
after his seat. Massie, of course, uh
now being primary by Ed Grin, who was
handpicked by Trump and obviously the AP
pack class to try and boost Thomas
Massie. So, uh here's a video uh that
you shared. Uh you said money bomb drops
on March 30th. I'm all in. This is a few
minutes long. We won't play the whole
thing, but you do have a cameo in it.
So, uh we'll we'll play some of this and
then we'll talk about it a little bit.
>> Ann of some vicious vicious stuff. That
of course is Thomas Massie.
>> The rift between Congressman Thomas
Massie and President Trump is getting
much more serious. [music]
>> The president's really mad at Thomas
Massie right now, but Thomas Massie is
not bought and paid [music] for.
>> Thomas Massie can't be bought, just like
Ron Paul couldn't be bought.
>> I sometimes call him the Ron Paul of
Congress. We call him Rand Paul Jr.
>> What he represents is an independent
voice within the Republican party who
believes in balanced budgets, low taxes,
and less foreign [music] war. We were
tired of endless wars in the Middle East
and tired of wars in Eastern Europe.
>> There's a big deal of overlap with
President Trump on that. All of the
things that [music] MAGA explicitly
voted for.
>> Do I prefer a neoconservative pro-war
Republican over Massie? Hell no, I
don't.
>> He is actually representing a lot of the
people in the MAGA base who are saying
we don't want this war. He's a bit of a
rogue guy. Since Ron Paul left Congress,
I've been saying publicly that Thomas
Massie is the best congressman [music]
in the country. This [__] we got to
get rid of this loser.
>> If you attack me, I'm probably going to
dig in. I'm not [music] bullied. He's
honest and he's tough fighting against
the cover up of the Epstein files.
That's what Thomas Massiey's doing.
[music] And Trump calls him a loser for
it.
>> The guy is a national hero at this
point. They're treating him like he's
treasonous.
>> They love voting there. They think it's
good politically. The guy's polling at
about 9%. [music] No, you're talking
about someone that is beloved in
Kentucky.
>> He's certainly been successful here in
the district. His nononsense libertarian
[music] flare has made him a Kentucky
fan favorite since 2012. This is how we
really truly drain the swamp. I'm with
Thomas Massie and Roana. Let's go, baby.
This might be one of these [music]
last stages where all of a sudden truth
breaks out. Ron Paul [music] raised big
bucks and some major eyebrows with a
very successful one-day internet
fundraising drive. Amazing. It's being
called a money bomb.
>> That's what his supporters call it, his
money bomb.
>> It's a one-day record for internet
donations. Paul lags in the polls, but
he has inspired a devoted following.
>> It was astounding and it astounded the
media and gave us a lot of credibility.
>> And who are his supporters? Well,
they're Republicans, their Democrats,
their independents, their young people,
old people. Anybody who [music] is
disenchanted with the candidates now in
the lead.
>> I don't hold grudges against anybody.
You know, you could say I [music]
disagree with with Thomas Massie, but if
you think Thomas Massie is the problem,
you are the problem.
>> I couldn't agree more.
>> He's fighting back and he has some
arguments that are pretty strong.
>> I think I'm going to donate money to
Massiey's campaign.
>> Okay, I wouldn't go that far.
>> It would be a tragedy if they get away
with lying through their teeth about
Thomas Massie. It's very necessary that
these money bombs be successful.
All right. I said I wasn't going to play
the whole thing, but I lied. Couldn't
find a good place to stop. Um so there
are areas where you know I have you know
ideological uh differences with Massie
but I think big picture and I DN you
this and part of my pitch to bring you
on because I think part of the purpose
of this conversation is I think to
communicate that like big picture we do
need not only a real anti-war movement
in this country but I do think we need
like an actual like liberty movement now
too. uh you could just feel a tension in
the air um like we haven't felt in a
very long time. You know, when Theo
Vaughn asked Joe Rogan the other day,
are we going to be okay? You know, like
there's just a sense of procarity uh
hanging over everyone's heads. And look,
I think uh there are a lot of peoples
around the world, Palestinians live with
that sense of procarity every day.
Cubans live with that sense of procarity
every day. People in this country have
lived with that sense of procarity. uh
every day, poor people, racial out
groupoups, all that. Um but now I think
everybody's feeling it. I think
everybody's feeling it. And I think
that's part of the shock [clears throat]
of this era. And so while I do have my
disagreements with Massie, I think I
could voice them to his face without him
sticking ice on me or calling me a
terrorist or put putting me on a list or
something. So I respect that greatly
about him. And his leadership on the
Epstein files has been great. His stance
on Gaza has been very strong uh as well.
So, how important is this primary and uh
do you think he will ultimately prevail?
>> Well, I'll start with yes, it's uh I
think he's going to prevail, but that
doesn't mean anybody should rest in
their laurels. Whether you have
disagreements with Thomas Massie about
economics or whatever your different uh
you know, disagreements are. I think
he's one of, if not the only honorable
person in Congress right now. So, I
would highly encourage people to to open
up their wallets and support the guy. uh
we raised 350,000 which uh you know for
a primary campaign in the GOP is like a
normal campaign budget but this is not a
normal race. They are putting up an
estimated like 23 $24 million to try and
primary him out of office. At least
that's what they've allotted to try and
take him out. I don't know if they spent
they haven't spent that much yet but
they have spent like five or six million
already. So, this is this is going to be
probably the most expensive
congressional race in the country and
maybe the most, you know, expensive
primary race ever. It's it's just
astronomical. So, yeah, I think he's
he's super important. I think he is the
air apparent to Ron Paul and I think
he's been about as, you know, pure and
as cogent uh anybody in politics in the
past decade since Ron Paul himself. So,
I think he's great and I and I love the
fact that he's creating kind of this
coalition. You know, Anakasparian
was in that that uh that promo with me
and Dave Smith and all these like
hardcore libertarians. And I love I love
kind of her exasperated
breaking down into
>> I think I'm I think I'm going to donate
to this guy. And it's like, yeah, I get
it. Um, you know, that's kind of how I
feel about Roana, even though I when he
talks about a billionaire tax, I want to
pull whatever hair I have left out. But,
um, yeah, I mean, we need honorable
people to do honorable things. So,
>> well, I I support a billionaire tax, but
I'm I'm willing to support Thomas as
well. Yes, I understand. Um, but, uh,
no, it I mean it is interesting. I think
like look like ultimately I think what
you're getting at here is something very
fundamental you know which is okay do we
have control over our government yes or
no because if we don't have control over
our government if our government is
completely unresponsive then it doesn't
matter what I think about a billionaire
tax versus what you think about a
billionaire
>> bingo
>> like the only reason our the only thing
that gives our debates meaning is if we
actually are able to exert control over
the political
system. Once that's gone, we can argue
all day about a billionaire tax. It
doesn't matter.
>> It doesn't matter.
>> I made that point on my my most recent
episode. Um like almost verbatim. I was
like, why does why does any of this
matter? Why do our disagreements matter
at all? If like if our government is
controlled by crony corporations and
foreign governments, but really
specifically Israel, then who cares? You
know, who cares about our disagreements
when it comes to economic policy? We're
not getting any of that anyways. We're
not abolishing the Federal Reserve.
We're not getting rid of the income tax.
We're probably I mean, maybe we'll get
some of the tax programs that you guys
want because the state likes to grow.
But aside from that, well, by the way,
this is actually why I think you guys
should agree with us on this is like if
you agree that we don't have any control
over our government, why should we be
giving it more resources? But anyways,
um yeah, I think that's exactly right,
though, is that we don't have control
over our government. Uh we're constantly
delivered a poo poo bladder of options
that like is literally poo poo. So, I
don't know. I don't know what else we're
supposed to do other than to come
together and and support truly
independent candidates, the ones that
have demonstrated that like they are
reviled by the establishment. And I
don't think that there's anybody more
reviled than Thomas Massie.
>> Yeah, absolutely. And I I felt that way
in 2016. I mean, I didn't vote for Trump
in 2016. His politics were never my
politics, and so I never supported him.
But I was rooting for him to win when
Hillary became the nominee just because
of how she ascended to the nomination.
You know, I was a Bernie guy and it was
so obvious that they cheated that I
thought to myself what I just said to
you now. If they can just steer a woman
like this to the nomination and just
install her as president, then what
difference does it make? Would any of us
think our debates have no meaning?
>> Yep.
>> So same dynamic with Kamla though in 24.
>> Yeah. I mean it was the exact same
phenomenon. It was I mean even more
egregious.
>> It was [laughter] Yes. Way more
egregious. Way more egregious. This was
a person who they clearly wanted to be
the successor to Hillary Clinton. They
ran her in 2020. She couldn't stick
around long enough to get a single vote.
So they install her as VP and then 3
months before the election he drops out
and she's the nominee. Like it was it
was outrageous. It was insane. And this
is why the the handrigging about the
threat to democracy that Donald Trump
posed just never was able to uh land
with so many people because the
Democrats functioned in such an
anti-democratic way that you could not
take seriously their hand ringing about
what a threat to democracy Trump is. And
in Trump's first term, he really wasn't
a threat to democracy. I think he is
now. But in the first term, I mean, when
you think about it, in 2020, if he
wanted to just end democracy, declare
martial law, and become a dictator, you
had an airborne toxic event, and close
to race riots. If that's not pretext to
just say, you know what, we're shutting
this all down. I'm King Donald. [__]
you. That's it. No election. That was
the pretext to do it. And he didn't do
it.
>> So, I didn't really have a reason to
believe that he would be, frankly, as
bad as he is now. Oh, exactly. I think
it's funny. Even though you come more
left and I come more right, but it's
like we we analyze this identically.
Like that's exactly how I felt about
him. I didn't vote for him in 2016. I
cheered on from the sideline because I
hate neocons and I hate Hillary Clinton
or neoliberals, whatever. Uh she's more
of a
>> same thing basically.
>> Yeah, exactly. Um so when he got in
there and he didn't start any major
wars, uh I thought, all right, well this
guy's better than the other ones. you
know, he's like he's not great by any
stretch. Um, and then 2020 rolls around
and it was like, all right, well, I I
studied that very deeply because of the
nature of my show being Liberty
Lockdown. I was really diving into the
to the research, the behind the scenes,
trying to figure out like, all right, is
this guy in on it or is he being duped?
And I really came to the conclusion that
he was duped. Uh, so now I have to
[laughter]
reassess all that, too. Maybe he wasn't.
But I really did think he was duped into
the lockdowns thing. So anyways, long
story short, you know, by the time, you
know, after you watch the FBI spy on him
illegally, they frame him for treason
with the Russians, there's all these
other things that like and the media
apparatics are going after him 24/7.
You just have to come to the conclusion
like, all right, maybe this guy is
really like independent, you know, maybe
he's like really, even though I disagree
with him on a ton of things. I'm not a
tariff guy, you know, but like
>> maybe he's for real
>> and then and then they try to kill him,
you know? [laughter] You're like you're
like, "All right, he's for real. He's
got to be for real at this point." And I
was wrong. Um, you know, funny story. I
actually was on a panel
>> the day of Butler with myself, Brett
Weinstein, Angela Mardle, and Cash Patel
went on to be the head of the FBI. It
was called, the name of the panel was
called How to Defeat the Deep State.
>> Wow.
>> And uh I, you know, it's just a
confluence of factors, but it's like,
you know, you're sitting up there with a
guy who then goes on to be the head of
the FBI and his his whole claim to fame
is that he's going to, you know, go
after the deep state and that he's he's
really big on this whole Epstein thing.
Dan Bonino is the same way. And RFK
Jr.'s talking about, you know, health
freedom and going against the vaccine
mandates and vaccine schedule for that
matter. Um and Donald Trump is the
president of peace and JD Vance is
feeding us some you know Austrian
talking points here here and there. Uh
Elon Musk is doing the same thing and
it's just like you you've got and then V
Ramos Swami who came on my show and I
got to debate and you know it's like
there's just so many reasons to think
that there's a chance at least there's a
chance that this is real and it just all
wasn't. It just all wasn't. And I And I
guess the biggest question for me at
this point is like was it was it fake
from the beginning? Has this been an
operation essentially to get him back
into power from a bunch of like very
intelligent actors that actually
targeted and weaponized the libertarian
voting block as minimal as it is to
their ends? or were some of these people
like true blue and they just all got in
there and they all blackmailed, bribed,
you know, whatever, whatever, whatever.
It's impossible for me to to really
dissect. And just one other quick story,
I also met and talked with Donald Trump
Jr. for an hour before I was on Tim Cast
IRL like year and a half, two years ago.
And and he was so redpilled in private,
[laughter] you know, you're like,
>> "Wow, that's interesting."
>> Yeah. You're like, you're talking to
this guy and I was talking to him. I I'
I've always said it was off the record,
so I'm not going to give any details as
to what he said, but I was talking about
uh the Las Vegas shooting, and I'll just
leave it at that, right?
>> I'm like, this guy is, you know, he's
not one of us, per se, but he's he's
closer. So, anyways, I'm just saying all
of these little anecdotal stories to
express or explain why I thought that
there was a chance that this was real,
and it just none of it was.
>> Yeah. I mean, I I think that there were
probably elements of that that were real
in the moment as far as they went. But I
think the overarching problem that just
became insurmountable in the long run
was that the guy is just completely
owned by Israel. And that's a segue into
this next piece. So, I want to show this
is a tweet that you made recently. This
is regarding the Iran war. every
American casualty, every plane lost,
every death, every child left without a
parent, every dollar spent, every cost
of living increase, every hardship that
this war creates, all of it is on Trump
and his inability to be a man and to
just tell Netanyahu
to [__] off. So, here is uh John
Kuryaku, former CIA officer, uh kind of
fleshing out this point here of just how
controlled by Israel Trump is making the
point that Trump is not the first
president that Israel insisted bomb ran
on their behalf. But he's the first one
who couldn't tell him no. Yep.
>> In all the years that I was in the CIA,
no matter who the Israeli prime minister
was, every single time an Israeli prime
minister came to Washington, no matter
who the president happened to be, the
Israelis would say, "Please help us bomb
Iran. Please help us bomb Iran. Please
help us bomb Iran." And the president's
always said no. until this one. I think
that President President Trump was duped
by uh Benjamin Netanyahu and now we're
in a war that that is not ours uh from
the beginning and that we cannot win.
And this is another thing too, my own
experience in the CIA and and at some of
the highest levels of government. I was
the executive assistant to the CIA's
deputy director throughout the uh the
Iraq war. There's never an exit
strategy. It's easy to attack a country.
It's easy to overthrow a government, but
then what do you do? That's the hard
part.
>> And he makes essentially the same point
here. Goes into a little more detail. Uh
this is a clip of Kiryaku on the Megan
Kelly show. years that I was in the CIA,
literally every time an Israeli prime
minister came to the United States, and
they come all the time, regardless of
who happened to be the president,
whether it was Ronald Reagan all the way
in into Donald Trump's first term, every
single Israeli prime minister would come
and say, "Please bomb Iran. Please bomb
Iran. Please bomb Iran." And every
president would say, "No, we're not
going to bomb Iran." until this
president and the Israelis from 1986,
the Israelis have have been saying that
the Iranians were 6 months away from a
nuclear bomb. Just simply not true. The
the CIA in the last 20 years has written
two national intelligence estimates.
Now, this is a sense of the entire
intelligence community concluding both
times that the Iranians did not have a
nuclear weapons program.
So it seems like what Kiryaku is saying
there is that Trump was the only guy who
Israel could convince to do this
convince in air quotes of course uh
since they have their own ways of
convincing people to do things. Um so
this seems strong evidence to me that
not only is Israel calling the shots but
that they needed someone as under their
thumb as Donald Trump to get the war
they always wanted. Now there's another
school of thought which is being sort of
debated on X right now. I'm sure you've
run into this debate uh in your own
circles which says that no, Israel is
our puppet and they're following our
lead because really it's Washington who
wants this war and that to blame Israel
is somehow to let Washington off the
hook. Uh so where do you land uh in that
debate?
>> Well, I'll give a straight answer and
then I'll give a nuanced answer.
Straight answer is this is Israel's war
like crystal clear. um nuance take is
that the people that argue that there
are pit bull um they're not entirely
wrong. I mean there are elements that
are in the military-industrial complex
etc that that donate to politicians that
have lobbying uh you know activities
that are trying to get politicians to
fight these wars but they are fighting
these wars for Israel like let's be
clear about that. Uh so I mean you don't
have to just take Kiryaku's word for it.
Uh, if you don't believe Joe Kent, then
you can dig into the actual history of
the Iraq war to find out how that all
played out. Um, I mean, the clean break
memo is huge. Uh, you know, PAC project
for a new American century.
>> The all the guys that got into George
Bush Jr.'s White House.
>> Yep. It's crystal clear that this was a,
you know, Jewish American, Israeli
Jewish movement to essentially use our
military to destroy all of Israel's
enemies and to enable them to take
Palestine like [laughter]
>> and beyond. Yeah.
>> Well, sure. Sure. It's Well, it's
expanded now because it's been so
successful. Um, but I'm not sure that
they actually expected that they could
go further than just taking Palestine,
but they are now expanding into like
little greater Israel projects. So, I
mean it to me it's like it's just
laughable that we even have to debate
this. Um, it's very frustrating and I
feel bad for Dave Smith because that's
now his career is he has to go around
talking to water carrying hacks like
Coleman Hughes to explain, you know,
just because the West Clark 7 isn't an
openand-shut case as to whether or not
that actually was, you know, provable
that he saw that that that was a plan.
We went and we took over those seven
countries. Did he guess that, [laughter]
you know,
>> come on, man. Um, and then you add in
all of the other things that we just
talked about
>> and there's so much more. you can get to
mere shimer and it's like there's just
ample evidence to be completely
convinced that Israel is dictating our
foreign policy particularly when it
comes to to the Middle East but I think
it also has it has its tendrils no
anti-semitic uh intention [laughter]
into uh
>> it has its hooks and it its horns into
that's better that's better [laughter]
I got to be safe um but the Venezuela
war man they were they are also
supportive of the Gazins. So, it's like
I think that they have sway that is
really incalculable. I mean, it's it's
astronomical. I mean, they were
deporting college students for speaking
out against Israel. It's like I just
don't know how like and I and I'm not
fond of many of the college
progressives. I mean, many of them would
like to see me [laughter]
tortured, but I still want them to be
able to speak freely. Um, so I don't
know. It's just all it's all madness.
And and then the obvious like op that
we've witnessed in terms of taking over
the influencer class, you know, the skin
suiting of MAGA and skin suiting of
America first is so so egregious and
obvious to me because I was actually
like deep in the weeds when I was
watching all these people that were
pushing the Kla Harris who's the
president of war, you know, or the
candidate of war and Trump is the
president of peace and gas is going to
be cheaper and no more wars. And then
they all flip on a dime and and I know
for a fact that these people are getting
paid. Like I know it. So it's an op and
there's like major money going into it.
And then you do the research, you find
out about Project Esther and you realize
that there's tens of millions if not
hundreds of millions if not god knows
how much money that's going into
propaganda campaigns that are
specifically targeted towards the
American people on Bennett on on the
behalf and benefit of Israel uh a
foreign government. Then you look in the
FAR filings and you recognize that like
basically [laughter]
the only country that's able to to do
this uh without running scants the law
seems to be Israel and it's just the the
double standards over and over again. It
just keeps coming up and coming up and
coming up. And then once you understand
the origins of of the war of of the wars
for my entire adult life and if you
don't know all the history then you can
go read Scott Horton's great books.
He'll lay it all out for you. But I mean
it's just like this is just this is not
a debate. this Israel is running the
show. I realize it doesn't make sense
because we're the big and powerful and
rich country, but it doesn't change the
fact that the actions don't make sense
unless you actually attribute them to
being driven on behalf of Israel.
>> Yeah. No, I think you're right. And the
the clean break memo highlights Iraq and
Syria. Syria was of course uh necessary
to knock off before the Iran war because
Syria was the most formidable country in
the Middle East like like militarily.
uh uh you know who could have uh fought
this war off uh on the Iranian side. And
so you know um it was uh or at least be
a stalwart against that kind of uh um
expansion. So it it really um when you
put everything together you know RFK
called Israel our aircraft carrier and
uh it may be true that there is a
strategic influence a strategic uh
benefit for the west to have a sort of
satellite state over there. Um, but at a
certain point, I think, you know, to to
deny that Israel is in the driver's
seat, especially when it comes to this
war because this war is so suicidally
insane, it's not even winnable. Like,
there's not even really an imperial
interest for us to fight it. We lost it.
We lost it in a in a week. We've clearly
lost it already. That's why Trump is
melting down now. So, yeah. I mean, I
think that that debate is just become
kind of a really frustrating one. I
think that's happening kind of on the
left and on the right. this question of
a chicken or the egg. Well, whose war is
it? You know, uh they clearly benefit
Israel. Go ahead.
>> Well, and I didn't even talk about the
fact that Marco Rubio said it was for
Israel and Donald Trump said it was for
Israel and Pete Heg says it was for
Israel. It's like what are we doing
here? Like it's obviously for Israel.
Yes, it was for Israel's defense. Um and
well, defense defense [laughter] after
they aggress, but you know what I'm
saying. Um, so yeah, it's it's totally
laughable and and I think that that's
that's been kind of the unifying talking
point that has allowed for probably you
and I to cross over or me and Ana
Kasparian or Stank or you know Scott and
Dave and all of us is like we just I
think that's really the tie that binds
is that we're all recognizing that we
don't have sovereignty. And I do want to
correct one thing that you said. It's
not your fault, but you know, I think it
was you said RFK said it that there are
aircraft carrier. That's been a very
common talking point forever. Sure. We
don't have bases there. Like like so if
there are aircraft carrier, you think
we'd be able to do whatever we want that
we'd be stationing our sordies out of
there. And it's like that's not how this
goes. Like we have bases in Bahrain and
Kuwait and Saudi and all these other
nations, but we don't have like this is
that's the other reason you know that
that they're not our pit bull or that we
are their pit bull is like we fight
their wars. They don't do [__] for us.
We fund their wars. We arm their wars.
We die in their wars. They don't do any
of that for us. None of it. And yet
people still argue that they're our
pitbull. It's like [__] They're our
pitbull. We are fighting people that are
our enemies only because we've been
fighting people that are their enemies
forever and now they hate us. That's as
simple as it can get. And it just drives
me absolutely insane that we can't just
all recognize it for what it is. And I
think it just all boils down to the the
curse of both Christian Zionism and the
the really successful campaign to
convince everybody that any criticism of
the nation state of Israel is somehow
bigoted hatred of a ethnic minority
whatever.
>> And I that that whole scam has to die.
It has to.
>> So
>> well I mean I think it is I mean it's
not working anymore. I mean, fewer and
fewer people are even bothering to
defend themselves against accusations of
anti-semitage. True. It's like I don't
even want to hear it. Like, don't even
bother me.
>> In our world, in our world, you're
right. But in day-to-day life, I think
it's it's a lot harder for people like
at the water cooler, you're probably not
talking about, you know,
>> right? Sure. Yeah. No, I think that's
that's definitely true. Um, all right. I
want to talk to you a little bit about
the cabinet shakeup here. So Trump
weighs broader cabinet shakeup as Iran
war pressure grows. US President Donald
Trump is considering a broader cabinet
shakeup in the wake of Attorney General
Pam Bondi's removal this week as he
grows increasingly frustrated with the
political fallout from the war with
Iran. Five people familiar with internal
White House discussions said any
potential reshuffleling could serve as a
reset for the White House as it
confronts a politically challenging
stretch. The five-week old war has
driven up gas prices, dragged down
Trump's approval ratings, and
intensified anxiety about the
consequences for Republicans headed into
November's midterm elections. Three
White House officials and two other
sources with knowledge of administration
dynamics spoke to Reuters on condition
of anonymity to discuss sensitive
personal matters. The sources did not
consistently describe any single cabinet
member as certain to lose their job in
the near term, but multiple officials
are in some degree of danger, they said.
Several of the sources said Tulsi
Gabbard, Trump's director of national
intelligence, and Commerce Secretary
Howard Lutnik are among those
potentially on the chopping block after
Trump ousted Pam Bondi and Homeland
Security Secretary Christine in recent
weeks. Trump has in in recent months
expressed displeasure with Gabbard, said
one senior White House official. Another
source with direct knowledge of the
matter said Trump had asked allies about
their thoughts on potential replacements
for his intelligence chief. So you have
Tulsi Gabbard, Howard Lutnick there on
the chopping block. And then the
Atlantic magazine reports separately.
Several people familiar with the White
House's plans told us there are active
discussions about others leaving the
administration, including FBI Director
Cash Patel, Army Secretary Daniel
Driscoll, and Labor Secretary Lorie
Chavez Darr.
Now, um
there have been some different theories
as to why Bondi was fired. Um do you
have any thoughts on that? And who do
you think might be the next to go here
since it seems like uh it's all kind of
unraveling pretty quickly?
>> Well, I would love for Bond to have been
fired for the Epstein cover up, but the
the early reporting was that she leaked
a potential or like a some level of
documentation for investigation into
Eric Swallwell and his
>> wife [__] So,
>> right, like I I I would imagine that she
was probably fired because she's just
not loyal to the to
the GOP in the way that or to MAGA to
Trump specifically. I mean, that's
really all Trump ever cares about. Are
you loyal to him? Do you say nice things
about him? Then he loves you. Um, and
then obviously I think Tulsi Gabbert is
on the chopping block because even
though she flip-flopped and ultimately
destroyed her legacy by lying about Iran
uh back I think it was during the
summer. Um
she when she was being questioned why I
think it was right after Joe Kent
resigned uh she she basically just like
she wouldn't back up Trump. She wouldn't
say that like yes they were an imminent
threat. Yes, we had to do this. The
president made the right decision. She
was just like the Trump you know the
president is the only one that can make
that decision. She just like kept going
back to that. And you know, as far as
Trump's concerned, I think he views that
as disloyalty because she wasn't willing
to fully colon pal pow herself, you
know,
>> right?
>> So that's my that's my justification for
that. Um I think anybody who's like even
a 5% real boy, which is kind of how I
view Tulsi, um a real gal, don't be
mean. Uh they they're all in jeopardy.
So the reason I think Letic hasn't been
fired despite the fact that he was
egregiously caught lying about his
relationship with right
>> Epstein that had extended a decade past
when he said it had ended and had been
you know numerous occasions when in fact
he said I met that guy once. It's like
[__] dude. He was caught red-handed.
So I think that obviously made him look
bad. But I think the reason he wasn't
fired already is because he's I I read
him as like a handler. Like that's how I
that's how I view him. I think I think
he is an asset to the Israelis. Um,
personally, so I'd be surprised if he
gets fired. If he does get fired, it'll
just be ceremonial. I mean, he'll still
be shipped off to go make a trillion
dollars stabbing Americans in the back.
Um
>> well you know my friend you know Russell
my friend my friend and my co my co-host
the other half of this project my friend
you know I got this friend of mine
Russell Davler who tells me no he um you
know he he makes a good point about
Lutnik and Scott Besson which is these
are the cabinet members who like get out
in front of Trump every once in a while
like every once in a while they'll come
out and they'll say okay when the jobs
come back people are going to be
building robots or you know here's how
the tariffs are going to go like they
will contradict Trump without fear of
retribution And that that's a sign that
they're actually running it. That
they're actually a lot higher up than
they look. Yeah.
>> You know who else does that?
>> Mark Levin.
>> Mark does that.
>> Absolutely. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> So, there's just something there's
something about [laughter]
the Jewish uh you know, orbiters to
Trump and how they're the only ones that
like get to basically safely oneup him.
And Netanyahu is the most egregious of
all. I mean, he can do whatever he
wants. Trump's like calling for peace.
He's saying, "Bring those bring those
planes back." And Netanyahu is just
like, "Fuck you. I'm going to bomb them
and then we'll talk about it after." And
Trump will get, you know, momentarily
publicly upset and then he immediately
rever reverts to basim where or baseline
where he's just like, "No, Netanyahu is
great, great leader. Well, you should
pardon him. Pardon him from his
corruption." It's like this guy is so
compromised. It's unbelievable.
>> I don't even know where I was going with
that, but it's just true. Well, no, it's
true that even like the cabinet itself
has been has been largely circumvented
to the point where, you know, this is
why I thought what Joe Kent did was so
significant and so heroic and not just
significant and heroic, but very prudent
and and very effective from a
self-serving standpoint. Like Joe Kent
has a future in politics if he wants it
right now because he stood on principle
and he quit. And if Tulsi Gabbard wants
a future in politics, she'll do the same
thing. I think her window has pretty
much closed now that we're a month into
the war. I don't know if there are too
many people who would give her too much
credit at this point. Uh but Joe Kent
did it when it mattered, when it
counted. And uh same for JD Vance. You
know, the reporting is that he's against
this war. Well, too bad, man. Too bad,
man. Like like nobody's voting for you
now. Like you're done. If you see the
betting odds of his his presidential
prospects, I mean, they have just gone
straight down because uh you know, at a
certain point, if you're not willing to
stand on principle for something this
consequential,
uh then how can you be taken seriously?
Like to me, if you're one of these
people who you you mentioned, you know,
the the the 5% real dealers, um they
they they got to quit or else they're a
zero.
>> Yep. No disagreement. Um, you know, I'm
already I was already very skeptical of
of both Tulsi, who I've met and talked
to a lot, um, and JD Vance, who I've
never met. And I was just like, these
people, they just seem like climbers.
They seem like they'll they'll be
principled when it doesn't matter and
total sellouts when it does. And
>> but I hoped, you know, I hoped and then
Joe Kent did it. I was like, I was
shocked. I really didn't expect that.
And you know, obviously everybody's
second guessing him, too, and they're
trying to smear him. But I I think
obviously what he did was the right
thing to do. Whether or not he's doing
it for motives of political, you know,
grandeur down the road is really
secondary to the fact that he did the
[__] right thing when he had to do
it. And that does take courage and he is
getting smeared and he is getting
investigated. And it's like these are he
took a major risk. So I I God bless him.
That's how I feel about it. And as far
as I'm concerned, anybody else in this
cabinet, not only should you not be in
contention for future presidential
hopeful, you should be in contention for
prison. Like that's how I feel about all
these people. Um, and for the record,
that's that's also how I felt about the
Democrats with the proxy war in Ukraine.
But anyways,
>> well, maybe these ice jails can be used
for, you know, [laughter]
duopoly politicians someday, you know.
Um, we can dream, right?
>> Um, all right. Yeah, we got big crowd in
here. 3435 in the YouTube chat. 8:20 on
Rumble. We're here with Clint Russell,
host of Liberty Lockdown. Go subscribe
to his YouTube channel. It's a great
>> is huge.
>> It's huge. It's huge.
>> Is Is that Is that big for you guys? I
don't even know. 35.
>> This is about our standard Sunday night
show. It's about our standard Sunday
night show. But yeah.
>> Well, then then it wasn't it wasn't a
drop off. That I told you we just had to
have a different Russell in here. We're
all good.
>> That's right. As long as you get a
Russell in here, you're good. Um I want
to respect your time. Do you have time
to do one more story with me? You want
to talk about Trump's Easter message?
>> Yeah, I would love to, man. I
>> His moving Easter message.
>> I've been venting all day about it. So,
go ahead if you start.
>> Let's do it. All right, everybody. So,
Donald Trump had a very heartwarming
Easter message this morning. I'm going
to let you listen to it from Jake
Tapper's uh mouth here. Now, get your
kids out of the room if you have them.
If if you show your kids this show, then
you know, you have bigger things to
worry about. But uh make sure you cover
their precious little ears for this.
Here's Jake Tapper reading Trump's
uncensored Easter message to Iran.
>> Has just threatened Iran in
extraordinary graphic terms, giving the
Iranian regime just over a day to either
make a deal, reopen the straight of
Hormuz, or face hell. If your children
are watching, be warned. The president
did not use polite language. Quote,
"Tuesday will be power plant day and
bridge day, all wrapped up in one in
Iran. There will be nothing like it.
Open the [__] straight, you crazy
bastards, or you'll be living in hell.
Just watch." We should note that
destroying civilian power infrastructure
is generally considered to constitute a
war crime under international law.
Though the president could argue that
the infrastructure has dual use and also
is utilized by Iran's military. Let's
get right to
>> I was about to say he he was going to
have to qualify that somehow because
Tapper is one of the biggest Israel
apologists in the media. So he had to be
like now you shouldn't bomb civilian
infrastructure unless of course you know
as he says it has dual purpose you know
then of course you know when when the
Jews do it you can do right but uh yeah
so he has
>> as if utilities don't always have dual
use as if the military can't use water
and electricity and I mean come on
>> it's a utility that's why it's called a
utility because it has multiple uses
that's why they're called utilities
>> because it has utility
>> right because [laughter] it has broad
utility exactly that's why they call
>> by the by the way you got to note too he
did not say The uh the last line he did
not say praise be to Allah. I thought
that was notable.
>> Oh, did he did he omit that?
>> Living in hell.
>> Cut it, dude.
>> Just watch. We should note that
destroying.
>> Oh yeah, look at that. Wow. I didn't
even catch consider war crime under
the president.
>> That's like serving a a Sunday without
the cherry on top. No. Praise be to
Allah. Wow. Wow. Good catch. I didn't
even realize that. [laughter]
>> Is he Jewish?
>> Oh, yeah. Of course. Of course.
>> Okay. I I didn't know. I I wonder if
that's why he didn't say it. It's
interesting. That could very well be.
Um, so yeah, let's read it again.
Tuesday will be power plant day and
bridge day all wrapped up in one in
Iran. There will be nothing like it.
Open the [__] straight, you crazy
bastards, or you'll be living in hell.
Just watch. Praise be to Allah.
President Donald J. Trump. This is like,
you know, he's treating the Iranians
like a bad improv partner. You know, in
improv comedy, the rule is you always
say yes. You never say no. That's a
block. And I was doing, you know, back
in my old theater days, I was doing an
improv show with someone who was a nice
person. They were a very good actor, but
they clearly were not versed in improv.
So, we're doing an improv scene, and the
audience shouts out, "Okay, you're both
janitors." And so, all right. So, I
start sweeping the floor. So, I tell
him, "Do me a favor. Go sweep up that
[__] over there." And he says, "No
blocks." And I'm like, "What the [__]
now? This scene is dead. This scene
sucks now." So, we go back and forth.
They say, "Sweep the floor." No. So,
finally, I just scream at him. I say,
"Sweep the [__] floor." And I
legitimately scared him and he went and
did it so we could get the scene back
going. That's what this reminded me of.
Open the [__] [laughter]
straight like he keeps telling him to do
it. They will not do it. And his only
play is to just get louder and louder
and of course threaten war crime after
war crime. So, here's Fox News finally
having to read this. It took them like
an hour to read this. And so, uh, here
is the Fox News reporter who apparently
talked to Trump this morning. So, he
reveals a few details of Trump's
conversation with him. And then he
>> There are bombshells in this, by the
way.
>> Oh, there are. There are. Yeah. We won't
get to all of them, but the biggest one
uh which I don't have queued up on the
video is that uh Trump claims to have
sent weapons to the Iranian protesters.
Yep.
>> Yeah. After they killed 45,000 of them,
he waited till, you know, that's why,
right? For reinforcements. Yeah, I'm
sure. That's not true though.
>> Exactly. [laughter] Yeah. So, here's uh
Fox News.
>> Good morning. I just spoke with
President Trump for 15 minutes. He gave
me some new details on the negotiations
behind the scenes with the Iranians and
what's going to happen if Iran does not
make a good faith deal. The president
tells me if they don't make a deal and
fast, I'm considering blowing everything
up and taking over the oil. The
president went on to say you're going to
see bridges and power plants dropping
all over their country. Now, I asked him
about the possibility of an agreement
with the Iranians. He says those who are
negotiating on behalf of Iran have been
granted amnesty at this time so they can
continue the talks. And the president
tells me he thinks he'll be able to get
a deal by tomorrow. He says, "I think
there's a good chance tomorrow." They're
negotiating now. All of this following
the president's true social.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Right now. Exactly. Yeah.
No, this this this tactic of uh
promising to bomb them back to the stone
age while insisting you're making
progress on negotiations. That's that's
worked really well.
>> It's it's very it's very key to
remember, too, though. He makes these
threats when the markets are closed and
then he then he says, "We're making
great progress at 8 8:59 a.m. East Coast
time when the market's open." You know,
>> that's true. That's true. Yeah, because
this is supposed to juice the market
now. So, I don't know. But you're right.
You're right. Yeah. There you are.
Right. right in the morning
>> where he talked about these negotiations
with the Iranians. We'll pull this up.
He says, quote, "Tuesday will be power
plant day and bridge day all wrapped up
in one." In Iran, there will be nothing
like it. Open the effing straight, you
crazy bastards, or you'll be living in
hell. Just watch. Praise be to Allah.
The president there on True Social about
this.
>> He just brushes past that on Fox News.
Praise be to Allah.
>> Pull this up. says, quote, "Tuesday will
be power plant day and bridge day, all
wrapped up in one. In Iran, there will
be nothing like it. Open the effing
straight, you crazy bastards, or you'll
be living in hell. Just watch. Praise be
to Allah." The president posting there
on True Social about this ongoing
operation and his new red line for the
Iranian regime. Now, the president also
provided new details on what happened
earlier this year as the Iranian regime
took to the streets and slaughtered what
the president tells me is 45,000
civilians in their own country after
that took place. President Trump told me
the United States sent guns to the
Iranian protesters. He tells me, "We
sent them a lot of guns. We sent them
through the Kurds and the president says
he thinks the Kurds kept them." Yeah,
that was the other big sound bite that
went far and wide. So, yeah, that was
>> massive deal.
>> Yeah. Oh, for sure. Uh, so Zed Galani
says Trump needs to be removed from
office. If JD Vance has any integrity
left, he would be working to achieve
this. The VP can't be fired by the
president. Your first responsibility is
to God and then to America, not to an
insane boss. JD Chris Murphy, Democratic
senator, said, "If I were in Trump's
cabinet, I would spend Easter calling
constitutional lawyers about the 25th
Amendment. This is completely, utterly
unhinged. He's already killed thousands.
He's going to kill thousands more." Yes.
Uh here is the Vermont Congresswoman uh
saying, "If President Obama or President
Biden had said anything remotely like
this, it' be non-stop coverage." uh on
every single channel
>> to fly under the radar and hope that he
doesn't tweet about them or truth about
them. It's all about their
self-preservation.
And so, no, I don't expect that. I would
like to see that, but it's usually only
just, you know, one or two people in
either chamber, and it's usually, you
know, very, very muted. This is
outrageous behavior from this president.
And I know that we've said it before on
this show and others that if President
Biden or President Obama had said
anything remotely like this, it would be
non-stop coverage on every single
channel and everyone in um the other
side of the aisle in the House and the
Senate would be howling about it and
demanding that they step down. That's
the reality. And so, no, they continue
to let us down with their lack of uh
courage, with their lack of moral
compass, and it's they're they're an
embarrassment. They're an embarrassment
to the country that they represent
Americans and yet do not stand up for
them.
>> I take I take this broad a lot more
seriously if she was calling for Biden
to be impeached over the Ukraine war.
But anyway,
>> well, of course, I mean, they all play
that game. They all play that game for
sure.
>> Well, that that's what that's what makes
the libertarians unique. That's what
makes Thomas Massie so special is that
he doesn't play that game. that he
opposition to to both of these. So
>> I mean the way the 25th amendment works
apparently is the vice president starts
the process. So that's why they're call
that's why Z gelani is calling on Vance
and that's why Chris Murphy said that
the cabinet should consult
constitutional lawyers because the way
the 25th amendment is invoked is the
vice president begins the proceeding
then they need a majority of senior
cabinet members to sign on and then if
and when the president says no I'm not
leaving then it goes to Congress for a
vote at this point what is the political
advantage to not
getting him out of office either through
a 25th amendment mechanism or through
impeachment, he's tanking the party. I
mean, the polls are just abysmal one day
after another, lower and lower and
lower. Like, not only does Trump not
really command the Republican caucus
anymore, I would argue he's a massive
liability to the Republican party at
this point. That became evident during
the Epstein files. Once they got the
218th vote to release the Epstein files,
what happened? Lots more Republicans
were saying they're going to vote to
release the Epstein files because now
they're getting released anyway and they
want to be on the right side of history
and on the right side of the voters come
the midterms. So at this point like what
do you think like isn't it in their
interest to try and have Trump removed
either through impeachment or the 25th
amendment?
>> Yeah, I'll be I mean it's very clear as
to why it's not is because if you go
against him, you're going against Apac,
you're going against Israel, right? and
and they will give you the Massie
treatment that they will put up a
challenger or if you already have a
challenger in the primary or in the
general, they will fund them. So that's
the whole reason it's not about
principle. It's not about even like
tactical benefit. Like I think you're
right. I think that in terms of like
voter popularity, all things being
equal, a lot of them probably would
abandon the MAGA Trump ship, but because
like the the the money that flows behind
any sort of uh left or right politician
who comes out in real
uh defense or uh objection to Trump or
APEC or Israel or the warfare state or
to the or the Iran war or Gaza for that
matter.
uh that's when you are really really
jeopardized as an incumbent to being
thrown out of office. So unfortunately
that that seems to be the biggest threat
that incumbents face. It's bigger than
anything else basically. So until that
changes, I don't know how we're going to
actually get enough courageous people to
do the right thing.
>> Yeah. No, I mean I think you're right. I
think that has to be the only if if if
the if a democratic will within America
was paramount then I think these people
would see it as in their interest to
vote to impeach Trump.
>> Right.
>> But obviously as you mentioned the will
of the people is not paramount. In fact
it's it's next to meaningless.
>> It's not it's not secondary. It's not
tertiary. It's like it's irrelevant.
>> It's irrelevant. Exactly. Uh, so here's
Adam Kinzinger who is a total piece of
[__] But I got to, you know, I admire a
good joke no matter who it comes from.
Poly market 99 to1 odds against the
president praising Allah on Easter.
[laughter]
>> Trump maybe.
>> Oh man, that sucks. That's a great
tweet.
>> Great joke. Don't you hate it when
someone you hate makes a good joke. I
hate that. I got to give it to you.
>> He's one of my least favorite people on
earth. That really hurts it. That's a
great tweet.
>> He's dreadful. But yeah, man. that well
that's that's what makes comedy great is
it's involuntary. You can't help but
laugh.
>> Exactly. Which is why by the way it's
very it's really funny too because
reading that tweet I don't think I've
ever been more angry at a politician in
my life this morning when I woke up and
saw that. But then hearing newscasters
have to read it. I was laughing
hysterically. I could not stop laughing.
So it is a it's an interesting
[laughter]
>> Well, I saw you tweeted that you thought
it was a fake and I thought it was a
fake too when I first read it. No, cuz
he doesn't tweet. He truths. So they're
all screenshots so you never know.
>> Exa Exactly. Exactly.
>> So like is this real? And then when you
see like 20 other people posting like I
guess
>> No. Then it was from the some White
House associate.
>> Yeah. The official account. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Did it. I was like oh my god. Um
>> but then one other one other point one
other point I wanted to make about the
impeachment question that you were
talking about. The other reason that
they're not going to do it is because I
don't think I don't think that they will
vote because they will be told that he
is fighting the war we want him to
fight. And all of you were basically
given a a pass on voting on the war
powers resolution to allow for you to
still go and pretend as if you oppose
this war and try and win your your
primary or win your generals. So shut
the [__] up. We're not We can give lip
service to CNN or whatever as to how
dangerous and insane he is, but when it
comes down to the vote, I bet you a ton
of Democrats and Republicans would would
vote to keep him. Tons.
That is a question. I mean, I think
Democrats would probably vote to bounce
him just because of the political
benefit, but Republicans, I mean, it's
interesting question. I mean, I think
we'll get that chance. I mean, I think
the Democrats are going to win the House
and they'll impeach him. So, we'll see
what happens at that point. Uh, but this
>> I mean right now before the midterms. If
it happens, if it happens after, then
yeah, maybe it'll be different,
>> right?
>> Rachel Blevens tweets out, Trump has 24
hours before markets open, so he has to
get all of his deranged threats out
before he comes and backs out and tells
you talks are ongoing and Iran is about
to capitulate.
>> He also needs
>> to distract from the US military's
costly mess of a rescue of the downed
F15 pilots. That's the other thing that
was so crazy about this is his previous
truth was announcing the rescue of the
pilot. Okay, so you have something
resembling a feel-good story. Not that
any of this is feel good, but he can
tout a victory and having recovered the
pilot. You'd think he'd want to like
cruise on that through the morning
shows, right? Let your let your uh let
your surrogates go out there and brag
about this rescue mission. And no, you
step on it with this [__] just
unhinged [__] [laughter]
It's just unbelievable. It's really
unbelievable. I mean, a lot of people
are saying he's demonically possessed,
and I'm like, "Yeah, maybe." [laughter]
Like, honestly, it's so it's so
deranged, it's almost hard to quantify.
Like,
>> he's losing it. I mean, the guy's losing
it. I mean, look, he was 70 in 2016. I
mean, the the the difference between,
you know, uh, uh, 79 and 69. That's not
the difference between, you know, 35 and
45. You know, you you lose a lot in
those 10 years. And uh no, he's clearly
he's clearly not playing with a full
deck anymore. So I like Mario,
>> something deeply wrong.
>> Something's going on there. Mario Nall
says, "If I had to take a guess, Trump
is not serious with these threats. This
is a bluff to force Iran to accept an
end to the war. And if it works, this is
a rosy rosy eyed look here. If it works,
Trump deserves his flowers for accepting
the war didn't go as planned and seeking
an off-ramp. Most other presidents may
have doubled down getting stuck in
another forever war. That's your read on
this that he's not doubling down. Open
the [__] straight or you'll live in
hell. [laughter]
>> Praise be to Allah.
That this is a sign to you that he's
come to his senses. Like what are you
kidding? What is that? A joke? Is this
April Fool's Day?
>> This is what I'm talking about with the
the bot and paid for influencers. It's
pervasive.
>> Jesus Christ.
>> It it just drives me absolutely insane.
There's like there's no rational read of
that that says that he's, you know,
playing for peace. I mean, that's
>> what the hell of it.
>> It's about as insane a thing as you can
possibly say. And and just for the
record, just so people know that like
I'm not some Trump derangement guy. Like
I voted for the dude. I thought that
there was a chance he was for real. I
recognize that this is like his cadence.
This is how he goes about diplomacy is
to talk like a lunatic. He did the same
thing with Kim Jong-un. Was it Ilun? I
forget. Um and then he Yeah. Yeah. And
then he crossed the DMZ and he met with
him and it was like so that was that was
good Trump, you know, talk crazy, be a
wild card, but then actually be
interested in peace. This version of him
is talk crazy, be a wild card, have no
interest in peace,
>> right? [laughter] Take your actual cues
from Mark Leavine and talk like a
[__] uh you know uh belligerent
drunk, you know, at 3:00 in the morning.
No, it's unbelievable because when he
won in 2016, as much as I said like I
didn't vote for him, but I was rooting
for him. And the night that he won, one
of my biggest regrets in my life, my
friend, I was living in Brooklyn at the
time, so New York City is a huge Hillary
town. And my friend, who is a big
libertarian just like you, was at a bar
in the village, and he said, "Come out
to this bar, you know, come out to this
bar with me. There are all these Hillary
people crying." And I'm like, "No, man.
I I was glued to my TV." Like I didn't
want to miss anything cuz to get to the
bar would have been like 40 minutes and
they didn't have internet on the subway
back then. So I would have missed a lot.
Like I don't want to miss it when they
call it like once in a lifetime. So I
didn't go and I'm like damn it I should
have [__] gone cuz that would have
been just so much fun to be in their
company when he won. So I was rooting
for him. But as so as like as exciting
as it was that he beat Hillary, the
thought did cross my mind. And I'm like,
"Okay, this is all fun and I'm glad it
happened, but this guy is kind of a
[__] lunatic. Like, what if he is
leading us during wartime? Like, won't
that be crazy scary?"
>> And luckily, the first time it didn't
happen, but here we are. Now it's
happening. And now I'm thinking about
like in 2016 when you stopped and you're
like, "Wait a minute. What if this guy
what if this guy brings us to war? Is
this the kind of guy you want leading
you?" Maybe it won't happen, but now
here we are. It's like that worst case
scenario in your head when I had, you
know, half a bottle of scotch in me
smoking cigars as he's winning. I'm
like, "Yeah, now that worst fear has
come true."
>> I couldn't agree more. Um, and as I said
when I in the episode where I announced
that I was going to vote for him. Worst
case scenario is, you know, war with
Iran that spirals into World War II.
[laughter] That's literally what I said.
Um, but I said, you know, I think it's
5% chance. No, not a super high chance.
And I was wrong. Um, just to also
explain a little bit more about why I
oppose it so deeply, aside from the
moral factor, I haven't even talked
about, you know, the financial factor,
which is really my expertise. I was my
background is as a finance guy.
[clears throat] We are jeopardizing the
dollars reserve status like in a way
that is
>> Oh, yeah.
>> outrageously egregious. Um, and what's
really fascinating is that many of the
Trump water carriers, Khan Inc. as I
call them, they have been even some of
the ones that are my friends like Tim
Pool, uh, you know, he would argue that
no, we have to do all of these wars in
the Middle East because it's about
preventing other countries from trading
currencies other than the dollar and to
a certain extent that was true
historically. So I was like, look, I
don't agree with it. I don't agree with
the empire. I don't agree with the fiat
system or the Federal Reserve, but I do
[clears throat] understand, you know,
how you actually maintain that strangle
hold on the financial system on global
trade so you can continue to just print
and borrow and spend to oblivion because
the only reason that you can is because
the money is diffused to the rest of the
planet. This is so different. I just
really need to the reason I'm doing this
long monologue is I really need to
emphasize this to your audience if
they're not aware. This is so different
because the whole reason that people
trade in the US dollar is because we
have been the policemen of the world
that we have controlled the waterways.
So that has enabled other countries to
not have massive expenditures when it
comes to defense because we will lay out
that money so that they don't have to.
That was the deal. You know, that's the
whole petro dollar system. This with the
straight of hormuz is the most insane
thing I've ever seen. I mean he is just
saying like everybody everybody for
decades knew you go to war with Iran
first thing they do is shut down the
straight everybody knew this right
>> now afterwards Pete Hexath and Trump and
others there's reports saying no one
pulled him this it was impossible for
anyone to foresee this coming but the
point that I'm trying to get to is the
fact that the president of the United
States would come out and say we don't
need the straight you guys need this is
just like it's announcing to the world
that you have to start trading in things
other than the dollar. That's what he's
saying. And I just for the life of me,
there is no tactical angle to that that
makes sense. Everything that we've done,
if you buy into that thesis, the the uh
petrod dollar hypothesis when it comes
to our foreign policy, none of this
makes sense. And I that's the I just
wanted to give this kind of cherry on
top of the Sunday as to why I know this
is for Israel because there is no way
any president would be doing what he's
doing especially when it comes to
straight hormuz because it is
jeopardizing our entire financial system
and therefore our entire empire not just
the GOP not just Trump's legacy. The
dollar's purchasing power is imperiled
existentially and you only do that if
you're working for somebody else and he
is.
>> Yeah. No, I think that that is uh
extremely well said and I think it was
also I mean all you had to do you didn't
need anybody to tell you Pete Hegathth
you just had to look at a map look at
how long the Iranian coastline is look
at what it sits on it
>> look at the [__] mountain ranges you
imbecile [laughter]
>> exactly
>> this is this is Afghanistan on steroids
I mean it's it's the craziest thing
we've ever done it really is I mean it's
right up there I I I have to immediately
walk that back because we did lock down
the world over a man-made pathogen and
we also had a proxy war with the largest
the two largest nuclear powers on Earth
and we didn't even pick up the phone to
talk to each other. So, it's a high bar,
but I think this might be the highest. I
mean, we just keep going
dangerously closer to the to the edge. I
I'm
>> Yeah, I think it's easily the worst
decision an American president has made
in our lifetimes. Like I think the COVID
response was a sort of cascading
bureaucracy, you know, that that just
kind of just ballooned. This is like,
okay, you're the executive, you say yes
or no
>> to invading Iran.
>> Trump's decision to say yes is the worst
decision by any president in our
lifetime. I think there's no question
about that. And it's it's really
remarkable, too, because a lot of a lot
of the Connie Quarter characters are
coming out and saying they're taking
that clip or that that quote about how
every president got the same intel and
every president said no and only Donald
Trump was the the brave enough to do it.
It's like you [__] idiots. That's the
you should read that the exact opposite.
Every other president was lied to and
said that Iran was days away from nukes.
And every other president said, "You're
lying Zionist propagandist and I'm not
going to do this and ruin my [__]
legacy." And every president was right
to say no. And he was the first one dumb
enough to say yes. And you are going to
you're going to tout that as him being
courageous? You imbecile. I can't
believe these people can even function
in life. I I don't understand it.
>> Yeah. No. No. You're No, no argument
there. So, I hate to I hate to feature
Michael Tracy unironically, but I have
to because the Wall Street Journal
article was paywalled and he found this.
So, uh Trump thinks the people of Iran
want him to bomb their power plants and
bridges. So, this is a this is an
interview that the Wall Street Journal
released uh with Trump today. But we are
in a position that's very strong and
that country will take 20 years to
rebuild if they're lucky if they have a
country, he said. And if they don't do
something by Tuesday evening, they won't
have any power plants and they won't
have any bridges standing. Asked if he's
concerned, the people of Iran, a country
of 93 million people, could suffer if
civilian infrastructure is hit. Trump
said, "No, they want us to do it."
Arguing the Iranian people are living in
hell. No, they they want us to commit
war crimes against them and bomb their
bridges and their power plants. I mean,
like I said, this is just truly
unhinged. I mean, he he is he's gone.
He's toast. I mean, his brain is soup at
this point. Um,
>> even the Hodge Twins are like, "Is Trump
okay?" [laughter]
>> Even the Hodge twins. Well, they make
that they point out a good thing. Is
Trump okay? I thought he said the
straight wasn't our problem. Yeah,
that's right. This was March 31st. This
was five days ago. It feels like two
years ago by now, but it's five, not
even a week ago.
>> He was he was saying it on the first and
second, too.
>> Yeah. No, just like a few days ago. He's
saying all the countries that can't get
jet fuel because of the straight of
hormones, like the UK, which refuse to
get involved, I have a suggestion for
you. Number one, buy from the US. We
have plenty. And number two, build up
some delayed courage. Go to the straight
and just take it. You'll have to start
learning how to fight for yourself. The
USA won't be there to help you anymore,
just like you weren't there for us. Iran
has been essentially decimated. Excuse
me. The [clears throat] hard part is
done. Go get your own oil. President
DJT. So less than a week ago, he's
saying we're not getting involved in
reopening the straight of whor moose. Go
get your own oil. And now it's open the
[__] straighter. We're gonna like it
is just it is
>> on Easter morning. By the way,
>> still warning.
>> I I mean the I'm I'm just disappointed
that he didn't open or end all of these
tweets with Alahu Akbar just to really
drive home how nuts he is.
>> Exactly. [laughter and gasps] So Kovi
says the [__] straight was [__]
open before he [__] started the
bomber. That's the thing. You're playing
just to get back to even. Like in
gambling they call this chasing it. You
sit down at the table, you lose a bunch
of money, and you spend all night
desperate to get it back. And you
usually just end up losing more. Like at
this point, the objective is to get back
to even. It's just insane.
>> Definitional sunk sunk cost fallacy. I
mean, that's that's all this is at this
point. Um and and the thing is,
>> you know, people keep saying like
>> I don't think I don't think any of these
people understand anything. You know,
it's like I'm not I don't have a
military background, but at least I've
read, you know, like I understand that
you cannot take the straight of Hormuz
unless you have a permanent force that
is able to put up a a defensive barrier
of some enormous size that's going to be
able to keep these boats from being
attacked because it doesn't require you
don't have to have like a functioning
military to stop shut down a waterway of
this size. You have to have like RPGs
and AK-47s just coming out from the
shore and then going back into a bunker
like you can. And not to mention
obviously they have missile capacity
that can do it then drone capacity that
can do it. I mean if you don't come to
an agreement with Iran I don't know how
you reopen the straight. I genuinely
don't. And like other than fullon
invasion million plus force draft like
you've got to go all the way or you nuke
them. I mean, these are these are his
options.
>> And it's just like none of this had to
happen. We didn't have to be here at
all. You're overtly doing this on behalf
of the donor class or whoever's got a
literal gun held to your head.
>> I just I what what really pisses me off
is that like the other people who maybe
aren't like literally existentially
threatened right now that they're not
coming out and going like he's he's
under threat. He's in he's under he's
under duress, whatever.
um
his sons, man. It's just I don't know. I
lost my dad in uh in October this year
or last year and it's just like
>> and my dad was kind of kind of losing
his mind at the end and I just it just
totally reminds me of you know that
feeling and I was like if how does Don
Jr. or Eric [laughter] not go either go
to their dad and try and take his phone
away, take his car keys away or go to
the media? I mean or something like I
don't know. It's just it's [__] it's
really scary. We're living through
dangerous times.
>> It's absolutely terrifying. It's
terrifying. So, Donald Trump says now
Tuesday 8:00 p.m. Eastern time. So, I
guess he extended the deadline a little
bit. Again, maybe that's to give the
markets some room to breathe. But, uh,
no, just just uh absolutely
terrifying.
So Marjorie Taylor Green reacted to
Donald Trump's uh Easter tweet once
again is Easter tweet. Tuesday will be
power plant day and bridge day all
wrapped up in one in Iran. There will be
nothing like it. Open the effing
straight you crazy bastards or you'll be
living in hell. Just watch. Praise be to
Allah. President Donald J. Trump. So
Marjorie Taylor Green had a very strong
response to this. She says, "On Easter
morning, this is what President Trump
posted. Everyone in his administration
that claims to be a Christian needs to
fall on their knees and beg forgiveness
from God and stop worshiping the
president and intervene in Trump's
madness. I know all of you and him and
he has gone insane. All of you are
complicit. I'm not defending Iran, but
let's be honest about all this. The
strait is closed because the US and
Israel started the unprovoked war
against Iran based on the same nuclear
lies they've been telling for decades
that any moment Iran would develop a
nuclear weapon. You know who has nuclear
weapons? Israel. They are more than
capable of defending themselves without
the US having to fight their wars, kill
innocent people and children and pay for
it. Trump threatening to bomb power
plants and bridges hurts the Iranian
people. the very people Trump claimed he
was freeing. On Easter of all days, we
as Christians should be reminded that
the Son of God died and rose from the
grave so that we can be forgiven once
and for all of our sins. Jesus commanded
us to love one another and forgive one
another, even our enemies. Now, here's
where she really goes for the throat.
Our president is not a Christian, and
his words and actions should not be
supported by Christians. Christians in
the administration should be pursuing
peace, urging the president to make
peace, not escalating war that is
hurting people. This is not what we
promised the American people when they
overwhelmingly voted in 2024. I know I
was there more than most. This is not
making America great again. This is
evil. So, that is perhaps as hard as
she's ever gone against Donald Trump,
saying he's not a Christian. I mean, of
course, she's taken a lot of this
personally as someone who has not only
supported Trump for a long time, but
really dug in to defend him when even
all of Washington was against him,
including his own party. I remember the
day after January 6th, maybe it was a
day or two days after, Lindsey Graham
was ready to wash his hands of Trump. He
said, "Yeah, there's some good things
that he did, but I'm done. This is" and
she was wearing CO masks that said Trump
won on them. Like, she was as loyal as
you could be through the worst of it.
through when it looked like Trump was
never going to have any kind of comeback
story to tell. And for her to come out
and now say he's not a Christian and
that this is evil. Yeah, that that's
probably her most damning statement
against him uh ever. What do you think
about that?
>> Well, I completely agree with your
assessment, but I'll just add that she's
100% right. Like he is not a Christian.
Um and I think that it's important that
people who are come out and say that
like he's not behaving in a Christian
manner. And I think that this is really
the bastardization of Christianity that
has radicalized Tucker Carlson into
becoming what I consider to be an
anti-war activist at this point. Like he
is really radicalized by watching people
skin suiting his religion and then
espousing death and destruction on
behalf of that religion. He is like
[__] furious about it. This is what
he got in a lot of trouble a month ago
or couple months ago for saying there's
no one he hates more. This is Tucker
Carlson. There's no one he hates more
than Christian Zionist.
>> Yeah, I remember that. Y
>> and then he walked it back and he said,
"I don't hate anybody." And d I know
exactly why he said that because that's
exactly how he feels that these are
supposed to be his people and they are,
you know, Judas or whatever. Um, so I
think that's I think probably MTG woke
up in the morning, had the exact same
reaction I did and probably you did and
just fired it off and told the truth
like the unvarnished truth, damn the
consequences. So, God bless her. I think
I think it's really important.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Me, too. And I think if she
can break with Trump in this dramatic
way, then really like like what is the
excuse for anybody at this point? Like,
if she can deprogram herself, uh, then
why can't some of the rank and file do
the same thing? And I'm just talking
about like people who will tell a
pollster, "Yes, I support Donald Trump."
I mean, MAGA also got MAGA would always
get criticized. They would always get
called a cult by the liberals. And I
always kind of defended them against
that charge because I always thought a
liberals were extremely cultlike around
Hillary Clinton, around Joe Biden, and
around Kla Harris, and just around their
general sort of orthodoxies
>> and Obama.
>> And Obama. Sure thing. Um, but I I
always kind of thought that, you know,
there is sort of freedom of thought
within MAGA. And I guess that was true.
I think this first year has sort of led
the freethinking Trump supporters to the
exits. And now what you're left with is
an actual cult.
>> Like I'm not saying everybody who voted
for Trump was in a cult. I'm saying like
at this point all of the freethinkers
have left the building. I think what
you're stuck with now is a genuine cult
of personality.
>> Well, not just a cult, but a death cult.
Like a cult. A cult that actually
worships death.
>> Yeah. I agree.
>> And I think that's that's what's so so
deeply concerning about it. I mean, just
for the record, like that's the reason
that I got on the MAGA bandwagon, even
if it was just a tentative toe, was that
like I saw in them a sincere what
appeared to be a sincere awakening to
the absolute catastrophe that was nation
building, that was our foreign policy,
>> right?
>> And and I did not see that amongst the
Democrats cuz if I had, I probably would
have put a toe on the Democrat
bandwagon. Um, but that it seemed
totally sincere and and now it's just
like their guy is doing it and half of
them have completely abandoned all their
principles. So, but I do want to agree
with you and, you know, say not all hope
is lost. I mean, when they say 30 when
they say 100% of MAGA supports Trump and
Trump says that you're only MAGA if you
support me, okay, well, then we already
know what we're dealing with, which is a
[__] poll that doesn't matter,
right?
>> Um, but also MAGA constitutes 30% or
less of the electorate at this junction.
So, it's like we're actually talking
about a completely dead political
movement. Like, it's not as dead as
Libertarian [laughter] Party, but it's
still dead in terms of winning general
elections, in terms of winning federal
elections. Like, MAGA is toast. So, it's
not a cult. Like, it's definitely not a
cult. You would never see approval
ratings get this bad after being as high
as they were, as rapidly as they have.
And the only reason that happened is
because MAGA wasn't a cult. But, it's
now completely demolished. and all of
the people who were not cult members are
gone. So, but it doesn't mean that it's
not a big problem. I mean, we have 30%
of the electorate, which are [__]
psychopaths and have no principles to
speak of. So, it's a problem.
>> Uh, yep. I agree. All right, Clint
Russell, thanks so much for being here
with us tonight. I really appreciate you
joining. Uh, you want to tell everybody
where they can find you?
>> Sure. Liberty Lockpot onx. You can
follow me there. And Liberty Lockdown is
the show. Glint Russell's the name. And
that's basically all I do. So, thank you
for having me, Keith, and I hope I
filled in for Russell accordingly.
>> Oh, you were fantastic. You were
fantastic. It was a great great
conversation. Really appreciate you
coming on. Hopefully, we survive this.
And if we if we survive this and make it
back to simpler times, I'll have you on
again. We could fight about the
billionaire tax, you know, but that
seems like a trivial debate at this
point when we're all about to die.
>> Um, so thank you, man. Really appreciate
it. Great pleasure to meet you.
>> Thanks for joining.
>> Thank you, guys.
>> All righty. Bye.
>> Bye.
>> It's Clint Russell, everybody. Round of
applause in the chat. That was a great
talk. Really appreciate Clint making
time for us tonight. We got a bunch of
super chats in Rumble Rants. Jake is in
the building tonight. Shout out to Jake.
We also got 3,998
in YouTube. [music]
>> And you do your own headbanging.
[music]
>> You know what I got to do? I gotta get
cuz he's going to be gone for a while. I
didn't even think about this. I got to
get my own u I got to order the prayer
bowl and the bell. I I should have
thought of that because it's not like
it's a one-off thing like he he's going
to be gone for a while. All right, I'll
make sure that we do that. All right,
before we get on with the rest of the
show, just want to give you a little
inside scoop that many creators are
talking about behind the scenes. It's
actually one of the reasons why we're
using Rumble because they made a way to
super chat us creators so we get paid
immediately and without any fees. So,
while YouTube and Twitch take up to 50%
fees when you tip us creators, this
method takes none. That's right. The
platform takes zero fees. We keep nearly
100% of what you send us. You can super
chat us with Bitcoin, Tether USD, or
even Tether Gold stable coins. The tip
will show up directly in the Rumble
chat, which of course we read throughout
the show. All you need to do is download
the Rumble wallet on the app store and
send the tips to your favorite creators
like us. You can also go to
wallet.rumble.com
or you can download the app directly
from the app stores. It's an amazing way
to get rid of the middleman and help the
creator economy. You can scan the QR
code, go to wallet.rumble.com
or find Rumble Wallet on the app store.
Sending a Rumble Ramp. Super quick,
super easy. Same as you always do it.
It'll just give you the option before
you send how you want to send it, USD or
through your Rumble wallet. Super easy.
helps us out, helps Rumble grow the free
speech creator economy. So, a shout out
to Rumble, of course, for making this
disruptive technology.
All right, we got a big crowd in here
tonight. Thank you all very much uh for
being here. Thanks once again to Clint
Russell. We still got plenty of show for
you all. I'm going to do a few segments
solo tonight before we go to the Q&A. It
is Sunday night, so we'll be going over
uh to a Q&A uh as well. Uh before we get
into Rumble Rants and super chats,
though, I do want to uh just share some
uh sad news with the community here. Uh
heartbreaking news from the Indie News
Network. All the members of Indie News
Network are so sad to see our friend and
sister Shondaanda Masta succumb to her
battle with cancer today. This was a few
days ago on April 2nd. She was a bright
light that will be missed by so many.
And I tweeted out, "A kind soul taken
far too soon. Spoke with her about a
month back. She was in such great
spirits. Ja was very brave and will be
very much missed." Yeah, I got a call
from uh my friend Pasta Jardulla. Uh
this had to be about a month ago and I
missed the call and uh good thing I
called him back when I did because I was
thinking h you know it was it was a
little late. I'm thinking maybe I'll
call him back in the morning but I'm
like
let me call him back right now. And so I
called him back and he had actually
flown out uh to be by Shondaanda's side
when she had taken a turn for the worse.
And she actually wanted to talk to me.
She wanted to thank me and thank the
show for, you know, promoting her uh,
you know, fundraisers and stuff like
that. And we we did very little u for
her. I wish we had done more. I wish we
could have gotten involved in in some
bigger way. Perhaps I wish we we had,
but uh the point is we we had done
relatively little. I mean, what we did
was easy. And uh she still when Pasta
was visiting her, she wanted to to talk
to me and say thank you. And so um you
know I spent probably about 5 10 minutes
on the phone with her and she was very
happy. She was she was in great spirit.
She was very kind um to be thinking,
"Hey, let me let me thank Katon. Like
what are you what are you thanking me
for?" I hardly did anything. But it was
uh it was very moving conversation. She
was in very good spirits seemingly
through the end. That was the last time
I talked to her and she had kind of ups
and downs and so we were all pulling for
her and um it's of course very sad uh to
see her taken this soon. But I did want
to uh give a shout out uh to the Indie
News Network and to all of our friends
over there. So go follow Indie News
Network uh on X and on Substack. Um and
you can learn more about Shondaanda and
celebrate her life uh over there. And so
condolences to her friends and her
family and her colleagues uh over there.
Uh we will certainly miss uh Shondaanda
de Masta. Uh and yeah, thanks to Pasta
of course for uh connecting us uh on the
on the phone that day because that was
that was the last time I talked to her.
Uh and so that is very sad, very sad and
she will be very much missed. Very much
missed. Uh Viicus Prime says
everything's a scam. Everything's a lie,
including the idea that rabbits [__]
each other to make eggs. [laughter] Lol.
Good one. Good one. Vienticus Prime. One
of my kids, uh, Sawyer, is into um,
nonsensical jokes. They're not even dad
jokes. They're worse than dad jokes.
They're like, they're jokes that make no
sense. He asked me the other day, he
says, "What did the tree say?" I said,
"What did the tree say?" He said, "The
tree said, knee." Get it? tree me.
[snorts] That would be a good joke book
to write. Just a a a book of nonsensical
jokes of jokes that don't mean anything.
I'm telling you, like he could be like a
YouTube star with that. That could be
like an Andy Calfman act. Just this
this, you know, little eight-year-old
kid that tells tells jokes that he's
really proud of that make no sense at
all. [snorts] Uh but that was a good
one. Vienticus, that made sense. Uh RB
Hams Beyond the Pale podcast says, "Get
up king last night was great. Ex-US
military Colonel Anthony Aguular gave
great insight into Gaza from an insider
POV." Yeah, Agular is great. Agular is
terrific. So congrats to RB on land in
that. That's awesome. Me shoot,
thanks for the super sticker. Thanks to
Jake for fielding these tonight, of
course. Vienticus Prime says, "Tell
Russell not to have any anime memes.
They just rounded up 800,000 people for
anime memes in China. Oh, interesting.
Maybe I'll send him a good one. Haha. Is
that true? Wow. Luckily, he's not into
that. He's not into that. But he's going
to be going live uh on his channel uh
throughout his his travels there. Um so,
you know, you can you can pass that
warning along to him. I mean, I will
too. Uh just in case. Remember that no
one hates your beef. Thank you, Mr. to
Silva. Appreciate that. Vienticus Prime
says, "Just because I feel the need to
say it proper. Everything's a scam.
Everything's a lie. Everything's
hypocrisy. And so you don't comply." Got
it.
Where would we be without you? If
there's not the perfect episode, at
least economically, that the enemy of my
enemy is my friend. It's this episode
with Katon and Russell. Love it. Yeah.
You know, I mean, look, like the thing I
like about the libertarians is that you
can disagree with them and they don't
want to throw you in [__] prison for
it. You know what I mean? Like, I can
have a conversation
with him. You know, you [__] disagree
with uh Jonathan Greenblat, he'll
[__] he'll he'll he'll [__] make a
phone call and there'll be the [__]
feds kicking down your door three days
later, you know? So, no. I mean, I I can
I can I can roll with the libertarians
for sure. Libertarians are ridiculous.
They want freedom for corporate
totalitarianism to be free from any
democratic influence. They claim to be
for freedom. Yeah, that that is one of
the contradictions I think in a lot of
manifestations of libertarianism. I
mean, I've been reading more about
anarchism lately since people would
often tell me I'm more an anarchist than
a Marxist. And I think you know certain
forms of anarchism involve sort of you
know voluntary collectivization that
doesn't necessarily need a state to
distribute resources but voluntary
collectivization of economic efforts.
Now that is of course utopian. That's
why like I'm not doctrinating I'm not
here to sell anybody on any theory,
right? Um, but you know, I think like
you can have a more
equal distribution of resources without
necessarily having a centralized state.
And I would I could talk with Clint
about that. It'll be interesting to see
what he thinks about that. But, of
course, that was not the purpose of the
conversation tonight. The purpose of the
conversation tonight was to uh you know
explore common grounds and common uh
interests and just a common framework
that you know and this one of the
reasons why he appreciated what I said
was like hey look um our policy
disagreements don't matter if we can't
influence the government. If the
government is beyond our influence then
you know I could argue with you till I'm
blue in the face and you can do the same
and it just it doesn't matter. Um, we
have to figure out a way uh for people
to start exerting some influence on our
government again. And I think we are
both in agreement uh on that. Um, Nong
Nong Nong, if the Dems win the House and
impeach Trump, $20 says it will be for
desecrating the rose garden or some such
[__] and not for war crimes or any sort
of oligarchic corruption. Well, maybe
they'll be like a real prosecutor and
just hit him with everything, you know,
just throw the kitchen sink at him.
Throw, you know, 50 counts. Uh, RB Ham,
so has Clint figured out yet that the
Butler incident was a psychological
operation? Trump is in the WWE Hall of
Fame for a reason. Thanks, RB. And
congrats on your Agular interview. The
crowd seems to have liked it.
Budy, thanks for the $5. DD and Liberty
Lockdown are both in my top five
mostwatched channels. This is awesome.
Pour one out for cat turret. Thank you.
Yeah, I like Clint's show, you know,
like I said, like, you know, he uh, you
know, even on the show tonight, he has
this kind of he has a soothing way about
him, you know, even though we're talking
about the same dystopian [__] you know,
he has this he has this calming
influence on you. Not like this show.
You listen to this show too much, you
have a [__] nervous breakdown.
[snorts] Uh, so that's why I like his
show. And I do like his show quite a
bit. Brad Gilbert. The butler bullet is
AI generated. Crop and tested. Paty
never reaches the roof. Apex can't shoot
down uh at Trump or crowd staged. They
don't give a [__] about Corey. That's a
dumb weak point. The they bomb babies.
FFS. Corey. Oh, you mean the
firefighter. I got it. Um
Brad Gilbert. F you. YouTube. 10 minutes
to write around your editors.
right around your editors. Not sure what
that means. Thank you though, Angry
Pearl. I hope everyone was careful this
Easter. After all, bunnies are deadly.
Just one nearly took down King Arthur
and his mean men during their quest for
the Holy Grail. That's right. That's
right. That has documented fact. Angry
Pearl, appreciate that. Uh, Peter
Monahan, Gator Pete, I'm late. Sorry. I
get it, but I can't afford but I need to
have a voice. A semblance of existence.
It's not much, but it's what I can do to
support you. Okay. Well, thank you,
Peter. I appreciate that. I appreciate
that. But please do be careful with
that. And it's call-in night, so you're
free to call in that you can do uh for
free. Angry Pearl DD, recently the Real
News Network wrote a follow-up article
on East Palestine, Ohio. Have you seen
it? No. Thank you for the tip. I will
check that out because I always like to
cover that story when I can, and it is
not easy to find that anywhere near the
front pages nowadays. So, I will check
that out. Appreciate it. I was part of
uh I was part of a fundraiser for East
Palestine with uh uh Savage Joy and I
believe Max Alvarez from the Real News
Network was on that stream. He wasn't on
with me. We each had like individual
slots, but I'm I think he was a part of
that. So maybe that was his article, but
I will I will check it out. Thank you.
Nong Nong. Ultimately, Israel is a
pampered US tankbait colony owned by the
deep state to provoke war in West Asia
and bribe and blackmail US politicians
and institutions. Indeed, mislead XX.
Thanks for the $5. US strategic
dominance of the Middle East is through
Israel. This idea that the US is some
victim of influence
is ridiculous.
Yeah, but it's it's not a victim of
influence. Like this is the like even
Norm fell into this thing, you know,
getting really hung up in the semantics
about saying we were duped or that we're
just innocent. And I I don't think any
of this says any of that. Like I don't
think the US is a victim of Israeli
influence. I think the United States
made a deal with the devil that we're
going to back Israel and that doesn't
mean that Israel doesn't take the lead
in certain situations like we're still
Yes. Of course, the United States is
still guilty of going into business with
a a murderous state like Israel. Like,
we're still guilty. Like, like the the
to say Israel led us into war is not to
say that we're a child that just, you
know, holds our mother's hand and they
they march us into a war that we want
nothing to do with. That's not to say
that at all. Um, so yeah, I don't think
one thing necessarily means the second
thing. Uh, Vienticus Prime, you know,
master blaster from Bartertown. Israel
is a master in the US is blaster. There
you go. If that helps. Yes, thanks.
Thanks, uh, Vienticus for uh, putting it
more poetically. Uh, Empire we are. In
the 90s, I was deep within the MIC. I
had the unfortunate experience of
working with Israelis. There's no
distance between what we have and what
we give to them. None. Thank you,
Empire. We are. French Laundry. free the
church of the holy sepulcher from
Israelis those regards it's Easter for
god's sake yeah so pizzaala did do a uh
mass there but the attendance was like
next to nothing next to nothing good
Friday was the the same thing the same
thing as I understand it the the Israeli
Jews couldn't even like gather around
the wall for Passover I think they have
the whole thing just like locked down so
yeah no really really just dreadful
situation
Clint getting smeared is called
character development. Part of the
counter up of getting out ahead of the
curve. Kent, Tucker, Candace, and Chump.
All ops. Peter Monahan. $5 already
missed Katon saving money to move to
Daang. $250 versus Yeah. $3,57 on 12:30.
Yeah. Well,
man, I mean, I don't know if Russell got
into specifics. I won't get into
specifics because I don't want to reveal
how much money he's spending, but it's
very, very little. like shockingly
little on like hotels and lodging. Like
it it's just unbelievably cheap to to go
there. Um, Professor Brown note Donald
pull out like your father should have.
Thank you. Vanticus Prime, why wouldn't
the president post on Truth Social
talking to the Iranians? Why would the
Iranian government have ever gotten on
to Truth Social? The Iranians keep
insisting that like they're not talking.
So, this is all just a meltdown. I mean,
it's all just a complete meltdown. Uh,
Peter Monahan, cheeseburger,
cheeseburger, cheeseburger, no soup for
you. Thank you, Gator Pete.
Uh, Kira Regina, thanks for the $5. If a
war fighter wants to put his war dick in
another war fighter's war assass, is
that cool with Pete? Asking for a
friend. Thank you, Kira. And by the way,
Pete Monahan, if you're tight on money
and you insist on on donating, which I
would really caution you against if
you're tight on money, man, because I
know you were having a hard time. Um, if
you rumble, you can rumble rampant for a
dollar a piece. Like, I really don't
feel comfortable
accepting donations if you're close to
the wall like that. Um, so just please
please be careful. Um,
Sparky, uh, look on the bright side.
President Trump's intellectual deficits
could lead to the demise of Israel. Iran
is a whole stack full of missiles and
drones to shower them for a couple
years. That's the thing. It's not even
in Israel's rational interest so much as
they're just absolutely psychotic. I
mean, you talk about a death cult. I
mean, if Zionism is not a death cult,
what is? Remember, says Sparky, Muslims
rever Jesus to Israelis, not so much.
Good point. Dementia is apparently
contagious. Trump is getting it from his
buddy Biden. All right. I've told this
joke before. It's not a joke. It's It's
a story. It's how I became friends with
one of my best friends for life. It's
Easter weekend. It's a good time to tell
this joke. True fans of the show going
back a while probably heard this before,
but it was uh it was I guess it must
have been around Easter weekend because
it was around the time when The Passion
of the Christ came out in 2004. And I
was in high school and uh you know, I
sat around a lunch table with a bunch of
kids. You know, this Roman Catholic
Italian kid was busting
my friend's balls because my friend was
Jewish and we weren't even friends at
the time. This is what made me want to
be his friend. So, he's busting the
Jewish kids balls. He says, "I saw the
Passion of the Christ this weekend. I
thought it was disgraceful what your
people did to Jesus Christ. Just the the
cruelty, the brutality. How could you do
that to someone? How could you beat them
and drag them through and then spear
them?
how could you treat our Lord and Savior
that way? And my friend says, "It seemed
like a good idea at the time."
That was his answer. That was a great
That was the best comeback that I have
ever heard. Like to this day, I've not
heard a comeback as funny as that. And I
knew we were going to be friends. And uh
the rest was history. Um whose effing
bingo card had praise be to Allah
replaces. Thank you for your attention
to this matter. Yeah. [snorts]
Yes. Good, good call. Uh, my real name
is just Katon. I was at a bar in San
Francisco after my friend's wedding when
Trump beat Hillary. Lots of screaming
and wailing. Good night to own a bar.
Yeah, I bet. My brother was at UPEN. He
was at law school, very liberal law
school. And they were watching the
results
uh in like a a theater, you know, they
had a big screen, you know, like a movie
screening room, like probably a lecture
hall that had like a pull down like
projector screens, this big sort of
amphitheater type room.
And uh there was one MAGA kid like in
basically the whole class. I mean, these
are all libs um at Upupen. And so, you
know, she's starting to lose. It's
starting to look pretty obvious that
she's not going to make it. And the room
just goes dead silent. Like, nobody's
saying a word. Everybody is just stunned
and depressed and miserable. And so the
MAGA kid gets up and he leaves the room.
Half hour later, he comes back into a
room that is just stone cold, silent.
Can hear a pin drop in this [__]
room. And Magga Kid comes back in with a
bottle of champagne and he pops it
[laughter and gasps] as loud as he can
in a dead silent room. The popping of
the cork just echoes throughout the room
and [laughter] he starts drinking the
champagne in front of all of these
traumatized libs. That's a scene. That's
a scene. Uh
oh, sorry. Got that one already. Um Brad
Gilbert makes perfect sense when you
were trying to reset your new digital
currency. Clint Trump was always a WEF
puppet. Everything was character
development. Thank you for that. Sparky
says Vance is likely waiting around to
be forced to remove Trump so he becomes
president. You may have asked Tulsi to
not resign so it's easier for her to
slide into VP. Uh well maybe maybe I
mean look my op I my projection stands.
The fact that there's even this kind of
talk about 25th amendment now makes me
feel like I'm on pretty good pace. I
said by the end of the year there's
going to be serious talk about him
stepping down. You know, not just like a
few ex accounts or whatever, but like
serious speculation that he's going to
have to step down. And, you know, we
still got nine months to go in uh 2026.
So, I I think my prediction is looking
pretty damn good. Uh okay. Uh let's do
some more segments. We got plenty of
more super chats and Rumble rants. and
we'll get to all that in due time, of
course. Uh we also are going to a Q&A
tonight uh after the show. So, plenty
more stuff. So, everybody uh strap in
and get ready. Got a lot more stuff uh
to get to here. All right, everybody.
So, uh, Trump is seeking to pay for his
new $1.5 trillion military budget by
cutting the following. So, yeah, it was
news, you know, about a year ago he
wanted to increase the military budget
to 1.5 trillion. And everybody thought,
well, for what? Ha. Well, jokes's on us
now, is it not? Now we know for what?
Uh, he wants to transition us to a war
economy. That's right, a war economy.
So, here are some of the cuts he's
willing to make here uh as put together
uh by this HQ news handle. Quite a few
of them. Grants for farmers and
agricultural research. Loans for rural
small businesses fully eliminated.
Support for farmers and food markets
fully eliminated. School meals and food
education for children abroad fully
eliminated. 659 million community
building grants blah blah blah. We go
down the line here uh toward the end uh
150 million for cutting edge clean
energy research. $4 billion
at the end there helping paying home
heating and cooling bills for lowincome
families fully eliminated. Now of course
that's not the last item on the list
which we'll get to in a second but that
is something that people are honing in
on. Trump re-ups push to eliminate
lowincome heating assistance program lie
heap. President Trump is once again
proposing to eliminate a program that
helps lowincome people heat and cool
their homes. The president's budget
released Friday states that the
low-income
home energy assistance program should be
cut. For the sixth time, the budget
proposes to end this program, it said,
adding that Trump's agenda should do
enough to lower energy prices and make
up the difference. Oh yeah, sure, sure.
It's not like they're trying to like
screw you out of your uh heating or
anything. It's not that they don't care
if you freeze to death or, you know, god
forbid you got a lot of seniors living
in these retirement communities in South
Florida and, you know, uh the Phoenix,
Arizona area. I mean, these could get to
be, you know, 110 120 degree days. You
can't have the cooling cut off. But, uh,
this looks like it could be a potential
problem here if he gets his way. Of
course, Congress is unlikely to actually
enact the cut as lie heap has
significant bipartisan support, but the
president's budget is an indicator of
his administration's priorities. The
Trump budget describes lie heap as
unnecessary because states have policies
preventing utility shut offs, making lie
heap a pass through benefiting utility
companies. So, this is actually the full
list of cuts that Trump wants to make in
order to accommodate his $1.5 trillion
military budget. That's right. To get
the whole list on the screen, I had to
zoom out so far that you can't even read
these things. So just uh just an
extensive list of programs that are
going to be cut, initiatives that are
going to be discontinued uh in order to
satisfy this proposed $1.5 trillion
military budget. Now Gunther Eagleman
responds to that list. This is a lie.
[laughter] Of course, it's not a lie. Uh
the community noted very quickly the
assertion that this tweet meaning this
the list of cuts to accommodate the $
one.5 trillion dollar defense budget or
war budget I should say. You shouldn't
be able to call it a defense budget if
it's not called the department of
defense anymore. If it's called the
department of war then we should call
the budget the war budget. It should no
longer you we should no longer be
allowed to call it the defense budget.
It's the war budget. The assertion that
this tweet is false is incorrect. The
listed budget reductions are documented
in the official FY2027
federal budget released by the White
House, which details reallocations from
domestic programs towards increased
defense spending. Again, shouldn't call
it defense spending if it's now not the
Department of Defense anymore. If it's
the Department of War, we should call it
war spending. So, if this seems like a
giant scam to you, you are not alone. I
have called MAGA the biggest scam in
modern political history.
Hands down. Stand by that 100%. And now
it seems like Tim Dylan has jumped on
this bandwagon as well. Here he is
calling the Trump administration the
greatest scam in history
>> about that there's not going to be any
more daycare
or Medicaid because of the war
>> because the United States can't take
care of daycare.
That has to be up to a state. We can't
take care of daycare. We're a big
country. We have 50 states. We have all
these other people. We're fighting wars.
We can't take care of daycare. You got
to let a state take care of daycare. And
they should pay for it, too. They should
pay. They have to raise their taxes. But
they should pay for it. And we could
lower our taxes a little bit to them to
make up. But we It's not possible for us
to take care of daycare, Medicaid,
Medicare, all these individual things.
They can do it on a state basis. You
can't do it on a federal. We have to
take
>> It's the greatest con in history, by the
way. It's the greatest con in history. I
mean, truly, it's the greatest. It's the
And I don't say great in like a good
way. It is truly the the most successful
con in history. It makes Enron look like
a guy doing three card monty on the
street.
um anything that you can remember and
identify as a complete and utter scam.
Um this is the greatest con in history
to run as an America first and you're
going to take care of America and then
turn around and go, you know, all of
these things, daycare, Medicare,
Medicaid, we have nothing to do with
that. We're fighting wars. That's what
we're here to do. We're here to have a
defense budget of 1.5 trillion and we're
here to fight wars. It is the greatest
scam in history. You got to hand it to
him. And I mean truly and not in you
know again not in like a not in a moral
way but like you got to hand it to him.
Um this is the greatest
about face
in political history that I have really
ever seen.
>> Uh yeah you got to hand it to him. You
gota more than you got to hand it to
him. You really got to hand it to
America because this is who we elevate
in this country.
You know, Trump is not an aberration in
that sense. The businessman, quote
unquote, the salesman, you know, the guy
who smiles to your face and then knifes
you in the back. You know, guy gives
that big toothy smile when he shakes
your hand and as soon as he gets you the
grip on your hand, he shives you in the
side with the other hand. You know,
those are the people who we consider to
be winners in this country. You know, we
act like those guys are sleeves bags,
but we don't treat them like that. We
treat them the exact opposite way. All
of us. All of us when we go to buy a car
or a new phone or whatever, you know,
I'll use the car dealership, you know,
as an example. You know, the car dealer
comes by, asks you about your life,
about your family, your kids, as if as
if he cares. He he doesn't care. We know
he doesn't care, right? And he knows
that. We know he doesn't care. Yeah.
Yeah. He He cares about my family, the
guy who's trying to sell me the car. He
doesn't close the sale with us. We can
wrap our van around the tree and die on
the way home. He wouldn't care one bit.
We know that. And he knows that. We know
that. But still, we go through this
ritual of being charmed and laughing and
joking and haha. We know his job is to
get as much out of us as he can. And he
knows that we understand that. You know,
it's like that scene in Fargo with the
True Coat. You know, the uh dealer gives
the guy True Coat for $500 even after
customer said uh he didn't want it.
YouTube was feeding me Fargo clips, so I
bit because I love that movie. And so
there's that great scene where, you
know, he agrees 195. Okay, we agree 195.
Then he comes and he hits him for
another $500 for the true coat. The guy
says, "What do you mean?" I said, "We I
I thought uh we didn't go for the true
code. I told you I didn't want it." He
says, "Yeah, but you know the true coat
that's done at the factory." He says,
"Well, [__] you." So then, of course,
dealer goes to the back room to ask the
the boss what we what what we could do
about it. Of course, he goes to the
boss's room and the boss, you know, they
just make some kind of small talk. What
are you doing this weekend? Blah blah
blah. Doesn't ask the boss anything.
Comes back to the customer. He says,
"Got some great news. Um, I can knock a
$100 off that car for you." And the
customer just eats it because, hey, by
that time, he's all in on the car. He's
already bought the car. He's not going
to back out of the deal on the car. And
so, he just takes it. Fine. He says,
"You're a [__] liar." Right? But so
what? the guy got you for the extra
$400. And in America, we look up to the
people who could do that the best. I
mean, Donald Trump before he ran for
president literally played a fake boss
on TV whose catchphrase was, "You're
fired." So, we watch this rich [__] sit
in a tacky, you know, pretend TV throne
and bully pretend workers around until
he fires them. That's what passes for
entertainment in America. So if that's
what passes for entertainment in
America, is it really a big surprise
that America would be scammed in this
way? Not only would America allow
themselves to be scammed in this way,
but when you walk around the country or
you drive around the country or drive
around town and you wonder as many
people have, hey, why aren't there more
protests in the streets about the war,
about the genocide, even about gas
prices? Like where's all the protests?
How is it that as a Trump voter, every
time you drive past the gas station and
you see these prices up in lights, you
don't feel like the world's biggest
sucker? And the answer is because you're
not the world's biggest sucker in a it's
it's a country full of the world's
biggest suckers. Suckers and scammers.
That's who lives in America. Suckers and
scammers. It's scam or be scammed. And
um you know, none of that is really
going to change. I don't think it's not
going to change unless there is uh a
revolution of consciousness in this
country until people start realizing
that they must not worship
sags,
businessmen, salesmen,
right? because it it it is that sort of
just like blind
uh uh acceptance of a certain dynamic
that the second you step out the door,
you are going to have your ass spread
open and someone's going to [__] you
till you bleed out. And and that is
essentially what is happening to America
right now. Donald Trump wiggled his way
into a second term. He's not running for
anything anymore. There's no reason to
give a [__] what you think about him
anymore. So, as soon as he gets in,
that's it. Spreads you open, [__] you,
and now we're bleeding out. That's
what's happening to this country. And
um, you know, I don't even know how
reparable it is. You know, I think it's
kind of the the DNA of this country and
it will remain sort of fundamentally
unaltered. I think sometimes a thing
kind of is what it is. You know, this
country was founded by a kind of a
bizarre group of people. They were elite
colonizers who themselves were also
colonized from an ocean away. And they
eventually figured, hey, you know, why
kick up when we could just keep the
whole loot for ourselves? And so they
led a revolution against the British and
they formed America as we know it. And
what did they do? They they created a
system that protected their wealth from
their own peasant underclass. And as we
expanded our territory out onto the
frontier, we kind of learned the virtues
of rugged individualism, right? life on
the frontier and it became ingrained in
us and at this point that is kind of the
American DNA. It's kind of just who we
are. You know, maybe not everything is
changeable. I don't know. I don't know.
Um it's worth a shot, I guess, as long
as we're here. Uh but I know it's no
surprise that a system built on greed
and gamesmanship and deceit
uh produced the ultimate con man,
supreme leader in Donald Trump. I'd be
very surprised if it didn't. I'd be very
surprised if it didn't. So, when Tim
Dylan says this is the greatest scam in
history, he's right. He's right. Trump
is really the end result of a country
that is just obsessed with all the wrong
things. Prioritizes is too weak a word.
We're obsessed with all the wrong
things. We value all the wrong things to
the exclusion
of all of the right things. give you an
example. As [snorts] long as I'm here by
myself, I can go on these tangents
without cutting into uh Russ's time. So,
my dishwasher broke. I'm at an apartment
complex. My dishwasher broke. Second
dishwasher that broke. The dishwashers
are garbage that they that they give you
here. Wasn't taking on any water. So, it
broke. So, I had to wash my dishes by
hand, which when you have three kids,
you you you really use the dishwasher a
lot. You don't wash the dishes by hand
very often. So, one of the only times I
washed the dishes by hand in this
apartment. So, I had, you know, when
you're washing dishes, I had uh, you
know, about a sink about 2/3 of the way
full with water.
And, um, apparently [snorts] that was
too much for the sink to handle. Uh, I
noticed the rim of the sink had become
unglued, I guess, under the weight of
the water. I said, "What the [__] is
that?" Two seconds later, the sink
bottoms out. Literally, the sink just
boom, falls [clears throat] out. the
drum. Water everywhere. We're in the
upstairs apartment, right? Six or seven
gallons of water. Maybe not that much. I
don't know how much the sink holds, but
a lot of water dripping out onto the
floor. It's the part where I know it's
going to leak through my neighbor's
ceiling. So, I run down to first of all,
I sop as much of it up with a towel as I
can. Um, you know, minimize the damage
as much as I can, but I know there's
going to be water coming through my
neighbor's ceiling. So, I run
downstairs. Turns out my neighbor's, you
know, outside. Do we have water? I said,
I know. My sink fell out. I was washing
my dishes and my sink just collapsed.
So, it's after hours. It's Friday night,
right? The management is not at the
complex. So, I call because I had a
maintenance emergency once a couple
years ago. And I know that if you call
after hours, you go to an operator and
they put you through to the emergency
maintenance person. Well, this time I
call the emergency maintenance and I get
a virtual assistant. I get AI, an AI
operator who's like, "Hello. Uh, what is
your problem?" I said, "My sink fell
out." She says, "I'm sorry to hear that
your sink fell out. Is there active
flooding?" I said, "Yes." She says, "You
should call 911 if it's an emergency. If
not, you know, what would you like me to
do?" So, I I said, "Put me I need to
talk to a person." Couldn't get through
to a person. She says, "We'll contact
the emergency on call." uh the emergency
on call maintenance guy. I didn't trust
that. I had to Google the number for the
actual human operator and then they put
me through to an actual maintenance guy
and the rest of the story is even
[__] crazier. But I don't want to
tell it uh yet cuz I don't want to get
anybody in trouble in case it is uh
discerned uh who who that person is. Uh
but anyway, I didn't get my sink fixed
until the next day. But anyway, the
point is you got a companies switching
to AI knowing that they're screwing the
customers. Like the the assumption is
when you replace a human with a robot in
that capacity, i.e. emergency after
hours maintenance
uh matters. You know that your tenant is
going to be less satisfied with that
service than if you had a person there.
They don't [__] care. They don't
[__] care. They know they're
providing you with worse service. They
know you know that. They know you know
why they're doing it because it's
cheaper. It's all that matters in this
country is how management saves money
and keeps more for themselves. That's
that's the only thing that matters in
this country. And so you ask yourself,
how do you walk around
in a country just so hypnotized by all
this propaganda? A country just
sleepwalking
into its own grave. Well, that's how and
that's how you have a country that falls
for this MAGA scam, which he's
absolutely right. I mean, it it is it is
the the ultimate scam. This is the
ultimate con. It's
>> what we're here to do. We're here to
have a defense budget of 1.5 trillion
and we're here to fight wars.
>> It is the greatest scam in history. You
got to hand it to him. And I mean truly,
and not in, you know, again, not in like
a not in a moral way, but like you got
to hand it to him. Um, this is the
greatest
about face in political history that I
have really ever seen.
>> 100%. When I was a tour guide, I had
this lovely old couple from South
Carolina. They're wonderful people, you
know, not bad people. And Trump was
running in 2016, and he's like, you
know, I think he could be a good
president cuz he has the money. He has
the money. Like, what do you So, what
what the [__] does that have to do with
anything? He has the money. That means
he'd be a good president because he has
the money. Well, yes. In a country that
values money, accumulation of wealth to
the extent that we do, the amount of
money you have in a lot of people's eyes
is equal to your virtue as a person.
Because the assumption is if you made a
bunch of money, you must be really
smart. And not just smart, but good.
Good.
Wealth is a substitute for virtue in the
American system. And that's how people
can be conned into this. And to go back
to that car salesman analogy in Fargo,
he knows once the guy bit for the car,
he can [__] him for the extra $500 on
the true coat that that he said he
didn't want. Of course he can. The guy's
already in. Trump he's in. You elected
his second term. He's a lame duck. You
don't need your vote anymore. Of course,
the salesman is going to put the final
[__] in your ass when you can't do
anything about it. And like every good
salesman, like every good con man, he
waited until you couldn't do [__] about
it to start a war with Iran. He didn't
do that in his first term because he
still needed your vote in his first
term. He didn't campaign on that for a
second term because he needed your vote
to get a second term. Now he doesn't
need anything from you anymore. And so
now is when now is when the ultimate con
reveals itself. Once you are powerless
against it, now he gives you that $500
true coat that you said you didn't want
that he knows you don't want. Gives it
to you anyway because he can. Nothing
you can do about it at this point. And
that's how that goes. Now, for what it's
worth, here is Will Rollins uh pointing
out how ironic it is that the No New
Wars president has started a new war.
Ironic, isn't it?
>> Something similar.
>> Yeah, 100%. I have buddies who voted for
him and to be honest, it surprises me
and I find it ironic that the no new
wars president has started a new war and
he's walked away from some of his
biggest political advantages that he had
when he won in 2024, like the economy.
And when you propose a $1.5 trillion
defense budget and you have your base
starting to perceive you as part of the
regular establishment in Washington DC,
you take away that advantage of being
the outsider candidate. And so I think
Democrats are probably going to be able
to capitalize in November on that.
>> Of course,
>> it's interesting that he mentions the
outsider candidate because, you know, uh
not only has this really tarnished the
Republican brand, but it has really
tarnished the outsider brand. people are
going to be much more skeptical of
outsider candidates now because they're
going to be uh you know they're going to
have the memory of uh Donald Trump fresh
in their mind. Last time an outsider
came along promising to change things.
What do we get? This right? This kind of
makes all outsiders
uh feel like snake oil salesmen even
though many of whom don't deserve to be
uh cast in that light. uh that this is
setting a not so good precedent uh for
so-called outsiders. And so the legacy
of this is just unbelievably
destructive. But this is a moment that
the country really uh walked into and um
we walked into it because of a lot of
priorities that this society has had all
wrong uh for for too long.
All right, we're going to go to some uh
super chats. In fact, Jake, if you could
throw up the uh scroll, please, and
thank you very much. Shout out to Jake
in the booth for helping us out
tonight's uh you can go to
dudesidence.comreon
if you like what we're doing here uh to
help us out for just $5 a month. That's
our scam. That's our hustle. Haha. We
give you a lot for it, though. you get
call-in access to all of our Q&As's
which happen every Sunday night after
the main show. Tonight is Sunday. It's
Easter Sunday, of course. How could you
forget with that glowing Easter message
that Donald Trump gave us uh early this
morning. Uh you also get adree versions
of every live stream uh sent to you the
day after they air. So adree live stream
replays. You also get our monthly film
club with RightBR TV's extensive catalog
of dissident cinema from around the
world. We had our second one, Cambodia
Year Zero, uh last week. We'll pick a
great one uh for April as well. Some
people want us to do a funnier one
because we did a couple of sad ones to
to start the series off. There are some
there are some cool kind of funny ones.
There's a kind of cool quirky Australian
horror film that I might pick uh for for
April. Well, I gotta wait for Russ to do
that because he's an Aussie. All right,
I'll figure out something. Figure out
something. They have a great They have a
great library of films. They have all
these great standup specials and
documentaries on comedians. Maybe we'll
do that. Maybe we'll pick uh uh one of
their uh sort of standup comedy uh
films. That might be fun. A little
change of pace. But anyway, you get
that. You also get postgame live stream
content and of course your name up in
lights plus the goodwill of supporting
independent media. We thank you all very
much for your support. Uh let's go to
some more super chats and rumble rants.
President Tel Aviv Toilet and BBN Nazi
Yahoo conspire with elites to end the
world. They want bunker class to retreat
so they can eliminate the masses then
emerge like maggots and rule over our
ashes. Thank you for that, Christopher
Back. Thanks for the $5. Katon, shameful
performance. What a weakling.
Sanewashing Trump. Perhaps we should
call you Jake Tapper. I sanewashed
Trump. I called him a madman. What do
you mean I sanewashed him? How did I
sane Donald Trump? I think we called him
an unhinged madman. Is that a joke or is
that a complaint? Uh, fun fact, I don't
think I'm guilty of sanewashing Donald
Trump, though. We'll take a poll in the
audience. I think I think you're in the
minority if that is your sincere
opinion. Uh Tim Pool's blown Netanyahu
for so long he [snorts] could start a
leaf blower. Thank you, Sparky.
Appreciate that. Stoop sign. Hey, Trump
isn't allowed at bridge day. Bridge day
rules are as follows. The bid opening
three, no Trump as the first bidder.
What it shows? A long solid minor suit.
Operative words, no Trump. Adore Jimmy
says, "Rest in peace, Sha de Masta."
Absolutely. Absolutely. Thank you for
that. Vienticus Prime, just smack a
small pot with something like a ladle,
Katon. It should work well enough. Lol.
Thank you, Vienticus. Oh, yeah. And
since Russ isn't here, how do you stop
an octopus with 10 tickles? Ha. Good
one. Good one. Yeah, I bought my uh I
bought my kid a a joke book um because
he's getting into telling jokes. There
was one in there that was pretty good
actually. That wasn't a dad joke, but it
was good. What was it? I forget what it
was. Uh maybe it'll pop back into my
head. That's the thing. When something
falls out of your mind and you're on by
yourself, you just have to let go and
keep going. You can't dwell because that
creates dead space. If I forget what I'm
saying and Russ is here, I can have Russ
read them. Read them and then I'll think
of it. But we're without a net here
tonight for the rest of the way. It's
just me. Katon, do a Star Wars segment
just for laughs. Ha, good one. Remember
when Biden was president and there would
be like, you know, five horrible stories
a week that you had to do and so you had
time to like do a pop culture segment
every now and then. Not now. Not now.
That's the thing about Trump. He, you
know, with with with Trump now, we have
like 30 horrible stories a week. We
can't keep up with all of them. So,
there's no way to do any of those.
There's no way to squeeze any of that
other stuff in. Uh, scary times.
Virtuoso. That Trump post was to pay
homage to his friend Mike Tyson, who
went on a post-fight rant about his
eventual opponent, Lennox Lewis, saying
he wants to eat his heart and his
children and then cap it off with praise
be to Allah. Is that right? Wow. That is
that true? I don't even know. I don't
even know if you're joking, Virtue. So,
um, but yeah, that would uh that would
be quite the quite the tribute that
people may have missed. Um,
Katon, you need a headbanging
bobblehead. Ah, I like that idea. I like
that idea. Thank you, Abu Kid. I really
like that. But, uh, for Russ's hiatus.
Yes. Bet you could find one online or
maybe even make one in AI for the 666.
No. No. I'm going to get a physical one.
No, I need that. I need a physical uh
headbanging bobblehead.
I need a prayer bowl. And I need a bell.
Uh, yeah. I'm I I'm going to be like a
Looney Tunes character here sitting here
with all this [__] bells and bowls and
papers and everything. But yes, no, that
is a good suggestion. I like it. Thank
you. That
that is using your brain. Uh heavy
snack. Jimmy encouraged defense of Joe
Rogan was so cringe I had to turn it
off. I won't let it ruin Jimmy for me,
but yikes. I mean, look, they're
friends, you know. We're going to talk
about uh we're going to talk about Rogan
and Theo Vaughn actually next. I got
that's that's my last segment. But, uh,
hey, look, you know, they're friends
with the guy, you know. I'm sure he's a
nice guy. I'm sure he treats his
friends, you know, well, you know, um,
you know, comics, it's hard for comics
to be treated well. You know, artists,
whether you're a musician or a comic or
anything, you know, it's hard to find
people who like treat you well. You
know, a lot of artists are always
exploited. So, to have like friends who
treat you well, like, I get it. It's
fine. Um, it's all good. They know what
we think and uh you know we know what
they think and it's fine. Uh Sedard
Vicious Katon the tree says now I take
my leaves.
Ah now I take my leaves. Good one. All
right. See? Good.
I hope Russ is watching. I hope Russ I
wish I remembered that joke. It was a
good joke.
What is the joke? Oh well this. All
right. So this is one. See, my kid
didn't get this because he didn't know
the previous joke, but it's um Why did
the gum cross the road? Cuz it was stuck
to the chicken's feet. Boom. Boom. Uh
Jake, you could you can kill the scroll
now if you're there. Uh thank you. We're
on the third scroll there. I want to
give them more than their money's worth.
Um why did the gum gu as in Mary cross
the road? Because it was stuck to the
chicken's feet.
Um, that wasn't the best one. No, there
was another one was better, but that was
not bad. [laughter] Thank you for
showing Chanda some love. Of course, she
hosted the Trailer Park Pundit channel,
co-hosted by beauty, co-hosted Beauty
and the Boomer every Saturday night with
years with Osave. Such an inspirational
and optimistic voice. Yes, very sweet
person. Very, very sweet person. Uh, one
of the many,
one of the countless injustices uh that
the world has thrown us. um in recent
times is that uh someone someone as kind
as Shondaanda was was taken as young as
she was. It's a it's very very sad. It's
very very sad. But like I said, she
seemed to be as far as I know and I
don't know much. I mean, I spoke to her
a couple times in my life, including,
you know, pasta put me through to her.
Um she seemed in in good fighting
spirits uh until the end, as far as I
could see. Um,
Mayal Shamsy, any news about Pure
Batista Pizza? I don't actually care. I
just like hearing his name being said.
Very musical. It is. That's the best
name ever. Yeah. No, I did give it um
somebody super chatted about him
earlier. Um, yeah, apparently they did
have the Easter Mass, but it was for a
very limited uh audience. They didn't
have the full service there, but
apparently they did go through with it.
Peter Jackson, it's not Israel
controlling the US or vice versa.
There's a secret cabal that runs both.
The USIsrael debate serves to obscure
this secret cabal.
Um I mean, yeah, that could be too. That
could be too. It could all be
bluepilled, you know. Um in that sense,
definitely open to that possibility. Um
you know me, Matt Brady, supporting the
concept of a wealth cap is now called
libertarianism,
the opposite of libertarianism.
Thank you. Flamma Blam Blam Blam.
Hell yeah, buddy. Have you been reading
Rudolph Rocker, Burkeman, Goldman, The
OG's, Zapatistas, and the News Wave
stuff? Which anarchist book would you
recommend? I haven't read any of that
[__] I mean, I'm still a father of
three. I don't really have time to read
that much. There's only so, you know,
there there's only so much I can read,
which mean there's talk about
libertarianism. There's a limit as to
how smart I can be with three kids and
how well read I could be. Uh, but I will
look into some stuff and uh recommend
what I can but takes time. Takes time.
Uh, but thank you for that. Raven Laz
RFK Jr. I Easter this freaky chick. I
hid six eggs around her house for me to
find. I found the first five. Guess
where the last one was? She knew me
well. That was a goose who ate a golden
egg. I almost did this story. Thank you,
Raven. L I almost did a story. It was uh
some study that showed that uh pig semen
has like cancer fighting qualities.
It was a real story. Some study that was
done that showed that you know pig [__]
can be used to fight cancer. And I
almost did the story just to
make that crack where after you read the
headline pig semen found to have
anti-cancer qualities. I was going to
say, "I'm not one to say I told you so,
but I told you so." That would have made
the whole segment, but it would have
been a very short segment because that's
the only reason I was tempted to do it.
Um, but that didn't make the cut. So, Z
Corman's Liberty Lockdown in the house,
libertarian who lovingly tunes into the
due dissonance commies from time to
time. Thanks for having Clint on,
fellas. Thank you. See, this is why I
like the libertarians. See, they're
nice. Nice. See, the the the left can
learn something from this super chat.
Okay, you don't have to be miserable.
See, you you can be nice. You can be
nice. See, I like that. Thank you, Z
Corbins. See, they know how to they know
how to build a movement. See, they're
they're nice to people. That that's
that's very important. Uh Peter Monahan
Keaton, check your email. Our president
using that language. How far we've
fallen from the very lowest branch. 25th
is my nuclear option. Can't stand him.
Thank you, Peter. Appreciate that. Uh,
Furrow Screen
says, "Guess which parent listens to
me." I say, "Russell's in China." So,
Katon's on his own for a bit. My mom
seems interested. My dad says, "Who's
that? I thought it was your podcast." My
mom says, "Hi,
thank you, Fear Squeeed, for that
update. Appreciate that." V. Nettles
bound says, "Hey, I like new Russell.
Please have him back on. Now we just
have to find someone with the first name
Dobular. Ha, good one. Uh, yeah, Clint
was great. Here's one for your boy. What
did the banana say to the orange? Hey,
orange. Love from Florida. Yeah, he
would like that. He would like that.
I'll tell him that one. I'll tell him
that one. Um,
Alex Dos Lee, thanks for the 499. Thank
you for your inattention to the file.
should be DJT's signature on his
troential
fetches. Yes, exactly. Vienticus, there
was just a huge $75 million lawsuit
getting refunds for car buyers in
Michigan. All from one auto group. Oh,
wow. Thank you for that. Uh, Stoop Sign,
I was the best men'swear salesman in
history because I didn't respect my own
company. To make my commission, I gave
[__] away for free so my company would
lose money. Company went bankrupt. Check
paid. [snorts] Thank you for that. Uh,
Vienticus says, "Say it, Keat, and say
it with conviction. Scream it out your
window if you have to. Everything's a
scam. Everything's a lie. Everything's
hypocrisy, and so we don't comply."
Thank you, Eio. Shush. You've had
libertarian economic policies since
Reagan. You can't push libertarians
policies on a public unless you mass
them via culture wars. And libertarian
policies don't work unless you wage a
war for resources. Yeah. No, I mean,
look, I'm not I'm not a libertarian. Um,
for sure. I think there are a lot of
unworkable things about it from from
what I could tell. End of empire, you
say. Hold my beer. The collective USA.
Username. End of the empire, you say.
Oh, sorry, got that one. That one was a
double. Peter Jackson, Zalinsky, Trump
both had TV shows. Pre-planned ops.
Yeah, both entertainers. Han Jh J
Han J. Is that what it is? To quote
another great movie, speaking of Fargo,
"If the rule you followed led you to
this, of what use was the rule?" Yes,
another Coleman Brothers, no country for
old men. It fed me that too, I guess,
cuz it was another Coleman Brothers
movie. I watched that scene recently as
well. That's the scene with the wife at
the end. Uh, masterpiece. Absolute
masterpiece film. It was a perfect film.
Absolutely perfect. From the first frame
to the last, there is literally not a
single thing about No Country for All
Men that I would change at all. Perfect.
From the first frame to the last, this
evening's broadcast of due dissidence
will be replaced with the Keat and Wise
Black Build Variety Hour. May God have
mercy on you scum sucking sleeves
worshiping soul Americans. [laughter]
Love it. You're the best. Thank you
[gasps] people infinite. Appreciate that
very much. I'm sorry Katon. I can't do
that. Says Danny. Danny. Thank you
Danny. Danny, appreciate that. Uh,
Vienticus says, "We should probably
start referring to a president's first
and second terms as buying favor term
and war term, respectively." Uh, yeah.
Yeah, not a bad idea. Not a bad idea.
Um, I think the Dems says, uh, Mike
Necron Fence, sorry if I mispronounced
that there. Uh, I think the Dems and the
mainstream left deserve a lot of the
blame for making this MAGA scam viable
in the first place. I agree.
No argument there, my friend. Appreciate
that. All right. Uh we will take the
rest of these uh in due time. Jake, can
you just do me a small favor and clear
out those that I've already read so that
I'm up to date uh on the last one.
Thanks very much uh for that. So folks,
we spent a lot of time here talking
about the hopelessness of the system and
how rigged everything is, whether it's
the war machine or the corporate media.
But there's also a rigged system hitting
your wallet right now, and that's
Medicare. So if you're approaching 65,
you're likely getting bombarded by
hustster agents pushing plans that pay
them a fat commission. That's right. A
lot of seniors get put onto Medicare
plans they don't need by agents seeking
a commission. We just did a whole
segment about how salespeople are
incentivized to screw customers in this
country. Uh because it's a total racket
and it leaves you holding the bag. Just
like in Fargo, they hit you with the
$500 true coat that you don't need. We
discussed that earlier in tonight's
lesson. But that is why we are partnered
with our friends at Chapter because they
are the only adviserss that compare
every single Medicare plan nationwide.
And their adviserss are independent and
unbiased. So they advocate for you and
not big insurance. If you call them and
you already have a Medicare plan that's
right for you, they will tell you to
stay put. And that will be the end of
the discussion. They are not
incentivized to sell you on things you
don't need because all of their agents
are salaried. So they're simply there to
help you find the best Medicare option
for you. The call is free. It's simple.
It's refreshingly honest. Connect with
an adviser today. This is a phone number
set up just for due dissidence uh
viewers. 404-76804.
That's 404760804.
So you're going to get to speak to a
person and they're going to have a good
sense of where you came from. Uh you can
also click the link in the description
of this video to inquire online. But
unlike a lot of companies that jerk you
around with infinite drop- down menus
and press one for this, two for that,
three for the other thing, uh you get to
speak to a person when you call chapter.
So the number is 404760804.
Give it a shot and find the Medicare
plan that is right for you.
All right, let's move right on along
here. We got one more segment uh here on
the evening that we're going to get to.
Let me see what we got over here. All
right, beautiful. All right, so Theo
Vaughn went on the Joe Rogan podcast and
things got pretty real here. This is
about 40 minutes into the episode. I did
watch, you know, a decent chunk of it,
not the whole thing. It was like 2 hours
and 40 minutes long. Um but uh here is
uh Theo Vaughn uh basically uh calling
uh Israel terrorists
>> think is going to happen? You think
we're going to be okay?
>> I hope so. Of course. I don't know.
>> Do you think about it?
>> I'm confused. I can't believe we went to
this war. I when we started bombing
Iran, I was like there can't this can't
be true.
>> And what about Lebanon now?
>> I know Israel's invaded Lebanon. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> And it's like just [__] stop it. What
do you need?
>> Well, they're trying to supposedly
they're trying to stop the terrorists.
>> That's [laughter] crazy though. Stop the
terrorists. What is it? 2002. Would you
fall asleep for fall asleep for 20
years? They're trying to stop the
terrorist. Well, well, here here he gets
gets the gets an answer for that.
>> That's [laughter] crazy though. If
you're the [__] terrorist,
[laughter]
>> you know what I'm saying? Like if you
want to stop them, [__] stand in
front of the [__] mirror
>> and start there.
>> Yeah. Yeah. To me, the thing that hit
hard is I brought this up to Clint
Russell was the beginning here.
>> What do you think is going to happen?
You think we're going to be okay?
>> I hope so. Of course. I don't know.
>> Do you think you think we're going to be
okay? You know, that resonates that
resonates with people. It resonates with
me. And you know, look, as I mentioned
with Clint on the air a couple hours
ago, different clip, obviously we're
clipping this separately, but you know,
I think one of the things that uh really
has given me a lot of perspective,
um, as someone of, you know, relative
privilege. I did not grow up rich. I
grew up middle class. I grew up a white
middle class suburban kid. And when you
start asking yourself, hey, are we
actually going to make it here? like
this is not like this is not at arms
length anymore. This is like hitting
home. You know, puts a lot in
perspective.
People around the world probably ask
themselves that question every day.
Palestinians, Venezuelans, Cubans,
Cambodians, where Russ just was. Even
people in America, poor people,
people of racial minorities in America,
they probably ask themselves that on
such a consistent basis that they don't
even consciously ask themselves that
anymore, right? That that is just that
is just part of
day-today life
in the back of your mind. That question
is just kind of running on a loop on
autopilot to the point where it may not
even be conscious anymore. Um, are we
going to be okay? You know, the way I
think of it is, um, you know, with
little kids now who are animal lovers,
we watch some like nature documentaries
and, um, we watch this documentary
about these lions and it's it's funny,
you know, you you you look at a lion in
the wild. Lions like just like chilling
out. They're like reclined. They're
rolling around. They're sleeping. and
they're rubbing their eyes. They are
just not a care in the world because
they're the top of the food chain. You
look at every other animal in a nature
documentary and they're
what's here, what's there, what's there.
They're always on high alert because
something's going to get them because
they're not top of the food chain.
They're not the lion. And I think
Americans, broadly speaking, and like I
said, there are gradations within
America, levels of privilege within the
empire, of course. Um, but generally
speaking, broadly speaking, Americans
are used to being that lion, right?
We're used to just being
sprawled out in the grass, just soaking
it in, knowing nothing's coming for us.
And now we're starting to feel, you
know, more like the antelope, more like
the Whoa. What's going on? What's going
on? Are we going to make it?
Um, so I think that that question there,
are we going to be okay? I think that I
think that cut pretty deep.
>> What do you think is going to happen?
You think we're going to be okay?
>> I hope so. Of course. I don't know.
>> Do you think about it?
>> I'm confused. I can't believe we went to
this war. I When we started bombing
Iran, I was like, there can't this can't
be true.
>> And what about Lebanon now?
>> I know. Israel's invaded Lebanon. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> And it's like, just [__] stop it.
What do you need? Well, they're trying
to supposedly they're trying to stop the
terrorists. [laughter]
>> That's crazy though if you're the
[__] terrorist.
>> That's right. That's right. That's crazy
when you're the [__] terrorist.
Um, so this is where it gets a little
awkward. This is where it gets a little
awkward because uh Theo goes off on one
of his more redpilled rants and Rogan
kind of pulls him back a little bit. Uh
telling him that he's got to come off
his medication because he's losing his
mind a little bit.
>> Cat and mouse game. People are like,
"We'll elect the Democrats next time."
It's like, but it's all the same [__]
has been happening forever. They haven't
been helping anybody forever. They're
letting [__] politicians slurp on
kids. All of our [__] money goes to
Israel and they're using it to [__]
genocide people. It's like everybody is
scared out of their wits right now. It's
like our religious leaders are afraid to
speak out and it's like the it's a time
where it's like Satan is amongst us and
our religious leaders are [__]
talking about [__] at the pole. It's
just like what is going I don't know
man.
>> We got to get you updepressent
[clears throat]
son. You're losing your [__] marbles.
>> You think I am?
>> Come hang out with us. Just chill out.
>> I'm here.
[laughter]
>> So he's on a tear there that he says,
"Whoa, whoa, whoa. You're on your See,
okay. We'll we'll get into this a little
bit more, but let me just play it one
more time.
>> It's all just a cat and mouse game.
People are like, "We'll elect the
Democrats next time." It's like,
>> but it's all the same [__] has been
happening forever. They haven't been
helping anybody forever. They're letting
[__] politicians slurp on kids. All
of our [__] money goes to Israel and
they're using it to [__] genocide
people. It's like everybody is scared
out of their wits right now. It's like
our religious leaders are afraid to
speak out and it's like the it's a time
where it's like Satan is amongst us and
our religious leaders are [__]
talking about [__] at the pole. It's
just like what is going I don't know
man.
>> We got to get you off those
anti-depressants son. You're losing your
[__] marbles.
>> You think I am?
>> Come hang out with us. Just chill out.
>> I'm here.
>> All right. As as Theo clarifies and
we'll get into this a little later. You
know he's joking when he says we have to
get you off the anti-depressants. They
had been talking about anti-depressants
earlier in the podcast. That's all true.
But it is ironic though that like of all
the crazy [__] that gets talked about on
the Joe Rogan show, like the most kind
of like clearheaded
redpilled like distillation of what is
plaguing the world right now is the one
that gets the response, hey man, you're
all right. You losing your marbles a
little bit. Like no, that that was
clarity that Theo was expressing there.
Like that was an epiphany moment. that
that was peak sanity, I think. Now,
Autism Capital, this is this account has
been on a journey because the they used
to be the biggest chuds
you'd see on X, both for Elon and for uh
MAGA and looks like they really turned
on uh Trump over over Epstein. I don't
follow them particularly closely, but
that's when I noticed a sharp change in
their commentary. Uh, if you watch the
full Joe Rogan and Theo Vaughn podcast
from today, you can cut the tension with
a knife. Theo will say something left
coded and Joe will immediately take the
opposite end of the stance and challenge
him over and over until Theo basically
says, "What are you doing?" Sit and
watch that part. Joe has a tendency to
do this from time to time. For some
reason, he randomly some episodes
decides this is going to be the one
where he's super combative and doesn't
let people just flow with the combo and
challenges way too much and the guest
can't get into a groove or cook. [cough]
Excuse me. It sort of makes sense why he
stops and challenges Theo on everything
right now because Theo jumps into
discussions about Israel, Trump, Luigi,
etc. uh like every hot topic
controversial issue and Joe wants to
make sure the heat doesn't blow back to
him or his advertisers. All right, so
this is kind of uh interesting here. Uh
before we get into the full context,
Theo Von says people are taking stuff
out of context and that's not fair. Joe
and I were having uh a convo about
getting off anti-depressants prior to
this prior and this a this is after
that. Joe has been supportive on and
off, Mike, about my well-being, like any
friend would, and I'm grateful. Thanks,
Joe Rogan, for having me. So, yeah, like
I said, like I didn't take that
literally. I took it as just kind of
this kind of ironic thing that uh, you
know, when he expresses such moral and
political
clarity is when you decide to rein him
in and suggest that uh he's gone off the
rails. He didn't mean it literally, of
course, but this is kind of interesting.
So this this is kind of when you look at
what led directly in to that previous
rant here which starts here
>> mouse game. People were like we'll look
at the Democrats next time. It's like
but it's all the same [__] has been
happening when you look at what came
before that. It's kind of interesting.
They were talking about and oddly enough
it's Rogan who brings up to Theo Vaughn
what a a murderous madman Christopher
Columbus was. and they start talking
about colonization and conquest and
genocide and that kind of flows into
Theo's rant there when Joe kind of pulls
him back. So, let's take a look at this.
>> Off that [__] bro. He was off that [__]
for sure.
>> Chris Co was off that [__] bro. That is
a great line.
>> Chris Co was off that [__] bro. He was
off that [__] bro.
>> Chris Co was off that [__] bro. So,
yeah. So, that that's talking about
Christopher Columbus.
Ah, should write a history book. Chris
Co was off that [__] bro. That's a
great title. That's a great title for a
book. That should be a book. No doubt
about it. That's amazing. Chris Co was
off that [__] bro. All right. So, they
get talking about Chris Co being off
that [__] bro. And then and then Rogan
actually
Rogan must have read at least some of
this book, People's History, or had or
had somebody explain it to him because
uh anybody who's read this book knows
it's most famous, I would say, for the
first chapter, uh where the brutality of
the European uh explorers uh is laid out
in extraordinarily uh disturbing and
upsetting uh detail. And Rogan
references some of that uh here uh
regarding Chris Co being off that [__]
bro.
>> That [__] bro. He was off that [__]
>> Did you ever read the things that
Christopher Columbus did when they came
to America?
>> He was a boss. I heard
>> he was an evil man, was he?
>> Oh my god. They would cut people's arms
off if they didn't bring them the right
amount of gold.
>> They were killing babies. Like they did
some horri
>> That's right in this book. That's right
in people's history. One of the things I
remember when I read this book for
jumping out at me that yeah, they would
uh they would make the people uh bring
them a certain amount of gold. And I
forget exactly what they would do. They
would they would award them with
something if they brought in enough gold
that they would like wear on their
person. And if you didn't have this on
your person, it meant you weren't
bringing them enough gold and yeah,
they'd hack your arm off. Really like
horrifying [__] horrifying [__] If you
haven't read this, it's obviously a a
must readad. That's why my copy is as
beat up as it is because with my ADHD,
it takes me so long to read a book like
this from cover to cover that by the
time I do, it's torn to shreds. But yep,
that's all in here.
>> [__] man.
>> Huh? They did horrific [__] to the
people that they found because they
found these people had gold. And you
know they like if you think about how
crazy it is that Mexico speaks Spanish.
You know how [snorts] crazy that is?
>> You know how crazy it is? That's so far
away from Spain.
>> Oh, that's a good point.
>> They all speak Spanish and they're
Catholic.
>> He says, "Oh, that's a good point." It
is a good point. It is a good point. Not
something you think of immediately, but
yeah, it is.
>> You know how crazy it is? That's so far
away from Spain.
>> Oh, that's a good point.
>> They all speak Spanish and they're
Catholic. Gee, where do you think that
happened?
>> Cortez.
>> Yeah, cool.
>> That [__] showed up in the 1500s
with like 600 dudes and 12 musketss.
They had like 12 They didn't even have
musket rifles. They had musket pistols.
>> He was a boss.
>> And they took over the whole [__]
country.
>> I know, dude.
>> Kind of crazy. Like, if you think about
all these years later, they all speak
Spanish now.
>> Yeah. That's nuts.
>> Well, do you think we could do something
like that now? Like, what do you think's
going to happen? Ron,
>> no. Just with I mean, like, I feel like
the [__] that's happening out there is
going to come here eventually.
>> Well, it most certainly will.
>> I think the [__] that's happening out
there is going to come here eventually.
And then Rogan says, "It most certainly
will." And then look, look where he
goes.
>> Yeah,
>> that's nuts.
>> Well, do you think we could do something
like that now? Like, what do you think's
going to happen with Ron?
>> No, just with that. I mean, like I feel
like the [__] that's happening out there
is going to come here eventually.
>> Well, it most certainly will. Yeah.
>> You know,
>> I mean, if [clears throat] uh Homeland
Security doesn't stop it tracks and
they're doing a great job of [laughter]
>> if Homeland Security doesn't stop it in
its tracks and they're doing a great
job. No, no, no. That's not what That's
not what Theo was talking about when he
says, "I fear what they're doing there.
They're going to do here." Don't forget
right leading into that was talk of the
horrors of colonization and genocide and
ethnic cleansing. At one point uh Theo
does bring up
Palanteer in this uh podcast and
educates Joe about Palunteer's role in
Gaza. So So when Theo says what they're
doing there they're going to do here. He
and then Joe says well thankfully
Homeland Security is stopping it. No,
no. That That's not where he was going.
That's not where he's going. He's He's
definitely misdirecting that.
>> Now, yeah, that's nuts.
>> Well, do you think we could do something
like that now? Like, what do you think's
going to happen?
>> No, just with I mean, like I feel like
the [__] that's happening out there is
going to come here eventually.
>> Well, it most certainly will.
>> Yeah. You know,
>> I mean, if uh Homeland Security doesn't
stop it
>> in its tracks, and they're doing a great
job of preventing a lot of them,
>> there's a lot of things that they catch
that you don't even hear about.
>> Terror cells they infiltrate.
>> Oh, yeah. Big Brother is protecting you.
It's all for your benefit. It's all for
your safety. That's right. That's right.
>> They know there's people in this
country. That was the most [__] up
thing about people being all nonchalant
about the border being wide open for 4
years.
>> You don't have to say non shaalon with a
French accent. You could just say
nonchalant. It's like an American word
in that way. But uh here he goes now
with the border stuff.
>> You don't even hear about that are like
terror cells they infiltrate and but
they know there's people in this
country. That was the most [__] up
thing about people being all nonchalant
about the border being wide open for
four years. Yeah.
>> Because men of military age entered into
this country from foreign countries.
>> What does that mean? 19 year olds. What
do you mean men of military age? Men?
Yeah. Some some men came in, some were
young, some were older, some were what?
Teenagers. So what? Military age? Again,
this is just this is not what he's
talking about.
>> We have no idea why. We don't know if
they're just honest people looking to
make a better life for them and their
family, send money back home. That'd be
best case scenario. But that's not all
of them. So what percentage of them are
terrorists? What percentage of them?
There's not it's not zero. Just a total
nonssequarter. It's just just totally
not what he was talking about when he
said they're going to bring here what
they're doing there. What he's talking
about, what Theo was clearly talking
about was surveillance,
brutalization
of people,
colonization. Look what Look what
America
is doing to Cuba. We We're putting them
under siege just like the Israelis put
Gaza under siege after October 7th.
Look at Palunteer's role in
policing
from the sky Gaza. Look at the role of
AI in targeting suspects quote unquote.
That's all coming here. Palanteer is
given this massive contract. That's what
Theo was talking about. Not talking
about military age men crossing the
border and thank God for homeland
security because they're stopping them.
That's just a a complete, dare I say,
deliberate misinterpretation of what
he's saying and misdirection of the
conversation away from what actually may
uh come across as a cogent critique of
colonization and surveillance and and
genocide.
>> It ain't zero. Yeah. But what also it's
like it's all just a cat and mouse game.
People are like, "We'll elect the
Democrats next time." It's like,
>> but it's all the same [__] has been
happening forever. They haven't been
[clears throat] helping anybody forever.
They're letting [__] politicians
slurp on kids. All of our [__] money
goes to Israel and they're using it to
[__] genocide people. It's like
everybody is scared out of their wits
right now. It's like our religious
leaders are afraid to speak out and it's
like the it's a time where it's like
Satan is amongst us and our religious
leaders are [__] talking about
[__] at the pole. It's just like
what is going I don't know man.
>> We got to get you off those depression
now. We got to get off.
Come hang out with us. Just chill out
here.
>> Just chill out at the mothership
tonight.
>> I do have to pee in a little while. But
>> you can pee.
>> I'm going to pee in a minute, man.
>> We'll let you.
>> But no, people are just scared, dude.
This is [__] that I can
>> They won't let you pee until you give
them your guns.
>> Really? That's how they're doing it now.
>> But what if you have to wash the black
face off the president? Can you [__]
use a little bit of piss had this big
dude?
>> And now they're on. See, now now they're
off it. Now they're off it. Now they're
back in uh their comfort zone there. So
I think that's probably a little bit of
what uh the Autism Capital account was
referring to when they picked up on this
sort of strange kind of tension cuz
yeah, didn't want to let him cook about
the things he was uh cooking on. Uh but
Theo got enough of it across uh to uh go
viral anyway. And like I said, you know,
they left on good terms. They didn't
have a blow up or anything like that,
obviously. Obviously. And the
anti-depressant thing was not literal. I
didn't take it as literal, but um yeah,
that is that is an example of a sort of
a sort of gatekeeping that that you kind
of sense there, especially since, you
know, Rogan led into that with, you
know, red pilling Theo. The the irony is
that that whole that whole exchange that
kind of went viral because of how
awkward it was. That whole exchange
started because Rogan actually started
red pilling him about
uh Columbus and about Cortez. And yeah,
I mean read in that chapter. I mean it
was it was a near elimination campaign.
I forget the exact figures but I mean
yeah these explorers came in and they
just they they killed almost everybody.
They killed almost everybody. That's why
you have European languages spoken
throughout Central and South America
now. It is it is a legacy of genocide.
And then uh you know once once Theo
picked up the ball and started running
with it uh at that point uh it got shut
down and misdirected into uh talk about
Canada's uh gun policy. Uh too bad. Too
bad. All right. Uh let's take some uh
super chats uh and Rumble rants and then
we will be headed over to Rumble for our
Q&A. We got a great crowd still in here.
3131 strong in the YouTube chat and we
got 958 over on Rumble. Please do smash
that subscribe button and uh come on
over to Rumble for the Q&A in just a
bit. Eio Shush says Trump is the second
biggest con in American political
history. Number one is the Republican
southern strategy that allowed
libertarians to dismantle the New Deal
and kill the middle class. That was uh
yeah, I mean that was in a way, yeah,
I'll give you that was probably more
sophisticated. Um but in terms of just
compressing everything into a expedited
timeline, I got to say this one. I got
to say it goes to this one. And by
modern political history, we're kind of
talking about like from that era on. I
don't know where you draw the line at
modern. I guess it depends how old you
are. But when I think of modern, yeah, I
think of actually like post civil rights
era. Um,
so depending on where you where you draw
the line, I guess. Um,
SASR
uh says, "You are doing awesome, Mr.
Katon. I hope Russell Davler stays
safe." Well, thank you, SASR. Appreciate
that very much. Katon, you're kicking
ass. Oh, thank you, Michael Steel. Keep
it up. Please tell Russell that I wanted
to wish him safe travels. You and Kurt
will be dynamite together. I can't stop
thinking of my trip to NYC. We are all
Persia. That's right. Thank you,
Michael, very much. And yeah, no, I
trust me. I mean, I think I'll get to
everybody. We We got a lot of shows to
put together. A lot of shows to put
together. So, I got I got guests host in
mind. We'll get to everybody. We got a
lot of stuff um on the way. Uh we got
Kit Cabello sitting in on Tuesday. Oh,
by the way, so Jose Vega looks like he's
going to get to debate Michael Blake.
Um, and hopefully Richie Torres. Richie
Torres has been invited to a debate. Uh,
I don't know if he'll show up or not.
Uh, but Michael Blake has apparently
agreed to debate Jose Vega. And so we're
looking at doing probably a
double-header stream on Tuesday, uh,
where I'll do the show with Kit and then
we'll live stream the debate at six
o'clock, uh, Eastern. It'll be a
90minute debate. I got to figure out how
to put that together. Um, but yeah, no,
we'll we'll get to everybody. I know we
got we got Kit on uh Tuesday and then I
got Rex Jones coming in on Thursday. Um
and then uh from there uh it is to be
announced. Not to be determined. I have
some I have some guest slots lined up
already, but don't worry, we'll get
everybody in here. It's a big family in
here. Uh Vanticus Prime, once I saw my
ex at the other end of a museum exhibit.
I wanted to talk to her, but I couldn't.
There was too much history between us.
Ha, good one. I like that one. I like
that one. Thank you, Vienticus.
Appreciate that. My real name, where is
Pasta these days? I like the way he
hosted the Jimmy Door Show. Pasta's
still working. Pasta still grooving.
Still making it happen. Uh, Gator Pete,
thanks for the $10. I get it. My first
go is YouTube, but I hear you. But
comfort doesn't equal strength. You have
to suffer somehow to appreciate what you
have. The yin and the yang. It's what we
used to fight for. Our breath. Love you.
Veto. Oh, that's very nice. Gator Pete,
thank you. Dave KBSC, have Rachel
Blevens on the show? She's been a great
on Ukraine and Iran Wars, but I've
rarely seen her outside her own show.
Yeah, I've never been in contact with
Rachel Bleven, but that is an idea. That
is an idea. Uh, I like that idea. So,
thank you for that. Yep. She does very
good work. Uh, indeed. Uh, Eio Shush, at
this point I think Rogan is compromised.
Not the Epstein kind, but Palanteer has
some dick pics you sent to that female
comedian. Would be a shame if the public
and your wife have found out. I I don't
necessarily think so. I mean, I don't
there's no way of knowing, but no, I
don't I don't have those. He he look he
he seems like a nice person to be honest
with you. Like he seems like a probably
a a good guy. Um, I think, look, man,
I've not I noticed this about his
commentary when he got the Spotify deal.
When you get paid a boatload of money,
even if you're a nice guy, even if
you're a good guy, I think somewhere in
you, you kind of feel a need to justify
that kind of wealth. you kind of feel a
need to justify that level of wealth
accumulation without feeling like you're
part of the problem, you know? And I've
noticed that like, you know, since he
got that big deal, like the thrust of
his political commentary is how like
rich people deserve to be rich and how
you shouldn't treat them too harshly
because rich people aren't bad.
I've just noticed that as kind of an
undercurrent. And I'm not a huge I'm not
a habitual listener like I don't listen
every episode. I I listen when there's a
guest on who I like and I've definitely
noticed that as kind of a a a shift. Um
but yeah, no like I I don't think Rogan
is like a bad person. You I don't get
that sense from him at all. Um and I
know he treats look he treats comics
really well at his club and gives them a
great venue and that's rare. Like that's
hard. like you're you're you're a
working artist, be there music or
standup or anything. You're used to
[__] dogging it for [__] pay and [__]
venues and [__] treatment. You know, a
lot of these [__]
the the ownership class in in the artist
world is uh is can be really scummy. And
so, you know, he seems to really not be
scummy in that way. So, I'll say that
for him. I just, you know, I think his
political direction since he took that
money is reflective of a guy who took a
lot of money and is worth a lot of
money. Like that's that's my take on Joe
Rogan. I don't I don't speculate beyond
that. Uh stoop sign like four months
ago, Israel made a campaign to get Theo
to try and whack himself.
That is dark. Joe is friends with Ker.
That was a 1/100th
of a Ker rant. 1/100th of a curve rant.
Thank you. Eio Shush Rogan spent years
trying to find Bigfoot. Now he's calling
people crazy for thinking Palanteer is
involved in the genocide that has been
broadcast to the world in 4K real time.
Well, yeah. I mean, that's the thing.
That's the thing. Like, you know, he's
indulged thoughts a lot crazier than
that. [laughter]
And now he's like, yeah, when when the
Pounder thing came up, he's like, well,
this is a biased source, right? Uh yeah,
I probably should have included that,
but I tend to uh I tend to air on the
side of focusing the pieces. Maybe to a
fault. Maybe I should have included
that. Um but we're at three hours
anyway, even with my trimming. So only
Europeans were brutal. Grow the [__] up,
you child. Did I say only Europeans are
brutal? Like did I say that? Like you
you have to you have to listen to what's
actually said rather than just like
project what you wish I had said. so you
could own me. Like if I had said that,
that would be a legit response because I
did not say only Europeans are brutal. I
I I did not say that. I did not say
that. So go and rewind the tape. Thanks
for the donation. Appreciate the uh
constructive feedback.
Always good to have constructive
criticism. But I did not say only
Europeans were brutal. I do not think
only Europeans were brutal. Citing the
fact that the European settlers in the
Americas were brutal does not logically
mean that I said only Europeans were
brutal. Uh so better luck next time, my
friend. Thank you for your support. JD
and Kurt still have their lips glued to
Rogan's behind. Like I said, they're
friends. You know what are you gonna do?
Um whoa, super ironic. Their Southpar's
gas field is actually located north of
Qatar's Northfield. Mind blown.
The South Pars gas field is located
north of Qar's Northfield.
Mind blown. Eio Shush. Unless Joe was
talking about Jewish men of military age
with billions of dollars and blackmail
to control the media and politicians in
America, then he was right about the
border. Pon Leon was a genocidist uh
too. Oh yeah, they were all brutal. They
were all brutal, man. It was horrible.
It's horrible. Very upsetting. I
remember reading that when I was a
teenager, man. Um and just Yeah, really.
I mean, you know, you always
re like when you read your school book
for like American history,
you read that yeah, these were brilliant
explorers who discovered America and
yeah, they did some bad things to some
of the Indians, but the overall
presentation of these people is as you
know, uh
heroic um discoverers
of great things. They don't they don't
put the emphasis where the emphasis
should obviously lie, which is in just
how awful awful is not the word. It's
beyond it's beyond words what they did
to the native peoples. And um yeah, you
you it's all there. First chapter of
people's history. It's a long chapter.
It's about 45 pages and it is uh very
very eye opening, very upsetting. Uh
whoa, super ironic. Southpar's
[clears throat]
gas field. Oh, I think we got that one
already. Is actually located north of
Qar's north field. Mind-blowing.
Jew on the go. Hey Katon, I have a
cowbell andor a prayer bell just like
the one Russ got that I'll be glad to
give you. Oh, thank you very much. That
That's not necessary though. I I could
get one. I could get one, you know. I I
can get one uh I can get one overnighted
here. But that that is very that is very
kind of you to offer. Uh just let me
know where to send it. Thank you for the
offer. But I I will I will get one. Uh
we could put that we could put that on
the company card. We can we can spare
that expense. But thank you though. Um
trying to think did I forget to do
anything? I don't think so. I think we
got everything done. All right. You know
what that means? That's our show
everybody. Thank you very much for being
here. Appreciate you all. We are going
to head to Rumble after a fiveminute uh
intermission here. Appreciate you all
very much for being here. Uh we will uh
be back on the air Tuesday 100 p.m.
Eastern with Kit Cabelloo and then we'll
be uh broadcasting the Jose Vega uh
debate that evening. Uh so thank you all
very much for being here with us. Eio
Shush says, "Thanks, Katon, for manning
the ship while Russ is out." Well, thank
you all for being here. Great crowd in
here tonight. Uh, thanks everybody for
spending your Easter Sunday evening with
us. Thanks to the YouTubers, thanks to
the Rumblers, thanks to the mods for
keeping the peace in the chat. Patrons,
paid Substack subscribers, and paid
locals members are invited to form a
call-in queue right now. We will uh
pause for a 5m minute intermission while
we head over to Rumble. Even if you're
not a paid member, all are welcome to
hang around in the chat uh and watch
along to the Q&A. Dudesence.comrumble
is the link. Thanks everybody for being
here tonight. Thanks to Jake in the
booth. We will see you in five minutes
if you're sticking around for Q&A. If
you're not, we'll see you Tuesday
afternoon, 100 p p.m. Eastern. Uh, until
then, be safe and be well. Courage.
Please clap.
[music]